<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="casting_info">
        <item name="info_1"><font face="sans-serif">Magic exists in the worlds of Star Wars in the form of powers. This chapter provides the rules for casting these powers. There are two major sources of these power: the Force and technology. While multiple classes use the Force or technology to fuel their powers, there are only the two sources. Regardless, powers follow the rules here.</font>
            \n\n   <font size="24">What is a Power?</font><font face="sans-serif">\n"   "A power is a discrete enhanced effect, a single shaping of the energies of the Force or a result of a technological formula, that creates a desired effect. In casting a power, a character carefully constructs the desired effect using the source of their power, and then releases it, all in the span of seconds.\n\n"   "Powers can be versatile tools, weapons, or protective wards. They can deal damage or undo it, impose or remove conditions (see appendix A), drain life energy away, and restore life to the dead.\n\n"   "A great number of powers exist, and over time many have been created and forgotten. An ancient force technique may exist in a long-lost holocron, or a piece of Rakatan schemata may contain revolutionary tech.</font>\n</item>
        <item name="info_2_Header">Power Level</item>
        <item name="info_2_Text">Every power has a level from 0 to 9. A power’s level is a general indicator of how powerful it is, with the lowly burst of speed at 1st level and the powerful greater explosion at 9th. At-will powers-simple but effective powers that characters can cast almost by rote-are level 0. The higher a power’s level, the higher level a force- or tech-caster must be to use that power.\n\n"   "Power level and character level don’t correspond directly. Typically, a character has to be at least 17th level, not 9th level, to cast a 9th-level power.\n</item>
        <item name="info_3_Header">known powers</item>
        <item name="info_3_Text">Before a force- or tech-caster can use a power, he or she must have the power learned, or must have access to the power in an enhanced item. Once a power is learned, it is always prepared. The number of powers a caster can have at any given time depends on the character’s level.\n\n"   "When you learn a power, either an at-will, 1st-level, or higher, you choose from the list of powers provided in Chapters 11 and 12. You can learn powers from any level up to your Max Power Level, including at-will powers. The total number of powers you learn in this way can’t exceed your Force or Tech Powers Known for your class.\n\n"   "If a power is granted to you by a class feature, that power does not count against your powers known and you can’t voluntarily unlearn it. If you already know that power, you may learn an additional power that is available to you.\n\n"   "Additionally, every time you learn a new power as a result of gaining a level, you can choose one of the powers you know and replace it with another power of the same type, as long as that power is not of a higher level than your Max Power Level.\n</item>
        <item name="info_4_Header">force and tech points</item>
        <item name="info_4_Text">Regardless of how many powers a caster knows or prepares, he or she can cast only a limited number of powers before resting. Manipulating the Force and channeling its energy into even a simple power is physically and mentally taxing, and higher-level powers are even more so. Thus, each casting class’s description includes a table showing how many force or tech points a character can use at each character level. For example, the 3rd-level consular Umara with 17 Wisdom has 15 force points.\n\n"   "When a character casts a power, he or she expends a number of points based on the level of the power to create the slot to cast it. At-will powers always cost 0 points, while casting a power at any other level costs the power level + 1 points, as shown in the Power Level Point Cost table below. When Umara casts project, a 1st-level power, she spends two of her 12 force points, leaving 10 remaining.\n\n"   "Finishing a long rest restores any expended force points, and finishing a short or long rest restores any expended tech points (see chapter 8 for the rules on resting).\n</item>
        <item name="info_5"><b>Casting in Armor</b>\n"   "Because of the mental focus and precise gestures required for force- and tech-casting, you must be proficient with the armor you are wearing to cast a power. You are otherwise too distracted and hampered by your armor for force- or tech-casting.\n</item>
        <item name="info_6"><font size="22">Casting a Power at a Higher Level</font>\n\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">When a caster casts a power using at a higher level than the power’s normal level, the power assumes the higher level for that casting. For instance, if Umara casts project at 2nd-level, she uses three force points and that project is 2nd level.\n\n"   "Many powers have more powerful effects when cast at a higher level, as indicated in the <b>Force Potency</b> and <b>Overcharge Tech</b> sections of the power’s description</font>\n</item>
        <item name="info_6_table_1"><b>Power Level</b></item>
        <item name="info_6_table_2"><b>Point Cost</b></item>
        <item name="info_7"><font size="22">At-Will Powers</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">An at-will power is one that can be cast without expending force or tech points. An at-will power’s level is 0.</font>\n</item>
        <item name="info_8_Header">casting focuses</item>
        <item name="info_8_Text"><font face="sans-serif">While forcecasting doesn’t require a focus to cast force powers, techcasting requires that you have a tech focus in order to cast tech powers.</font>
            \n\n<font size="24">Casting a Power</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">When a character casts any power, the same basic rules are followed, regardless of the character’s class or the power’s effects.\n\n"   "Each power description in chapters 11 and 12 begins with a block of information, including the power’s name, level, alignment (for Force powers), prerequisites (if it has any), casting time, range, and duration. The rest of a power entry describes the power’s effect.</font>\n</item>
        <item name="info_9_Header">power alignments</item>
        <item name="info_9_Text">Most force powers are aligned with one of the opposing sides of the Force-light and dark-while many fall somewhere in the middle-universal. You use your Wisdom for light side powers, Charisma for dark side powers, and Wisdom or Charisma for universal powers (your choice). Additionally, certain archetypes and feats offer benefits to using powers of a specific alignment.\n</item>
        <item name="info_10_Header">prerequisites</item>
        <item name="info_10_Text">Certain force powers are built as more powerful version of previous powers. They require that you know the previous power before you can learn the new one, and you must retain knowledge of the previous power to be able to cast the new one. If you are learning two or more powers at the same time, you can learn a power at the same time that you learn its prerequisites.\n\n"   "For instance, to learn the knight speed force power you would first need to learn the burst of speed power, as indicated by its prerequisites.\n</item>
        <item name="info_11_Header">casting time</item>
        <item name="info_11_Text"><font face="sans-serif">Most powers require a single action to cast, but some powers require a bonus action, a reaction, or much more time to cast.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Bonus Action</font><font face="sans-serif">\n"   "A power cast with a bonus action is especially swift. You can only cast one 1st-level or higher power using your action or bonus action on each of your turns. Once you’ve done so, you can only cast at-will powers with your action or bonus action on this turn.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Reactions</font><font face="sans-serif">\n"   "Some powers can be cast as reactions. These powers take a fraction of a second to bring about and are cast in response to some event. If a power can be cast as a reaction, the power’s description tells you exactly when you can do so.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Longer Casting Times</font><font face="sans-serif">\n"   "Certain powers require more time to cast: minutes or even hours. When you cast a power with a casting time longer than a single action or reaction, you must spend your action each turn casting the power, and you must maintain your concentration while you do so (see “Concentration” below). If your concentration is broken, the power fails, but you don’t expend force or tech points. If you want to try casting the power again, you must start over.</font>\n</item>
        <item name="info_12_Header">range</item>
        <item name="info_12_Text">The target of a power must be within the power’s range. For a power like shock, the target is a creature. For a power like explosion, the target is the point in space where the explosion occurs.\n\n"   "Most powers have ranges expressed in feet. Some powers can target only a creature (including you) that you touch. Other powers, such as the shield power, affect only you. These powers have a range of self.\n\n"   "Powers that create cones or lines of effect that originate from you also have a range of self, indicating that the origin point of the power’s effect must be you (see “Areas of Effect” later in this chapter).\n\n"   "Once a power is cast, its effects aren’t limited by its range, unless the power’s description says otherwise.\n</item>
        <item name="info_13_Header">duration</item>
        <item name="info_13_Text"><font face="sans-serif">A power’s duration is the length of time the power persists. A duration can be expressed in rounds, minutes, hours, or even years. Some powers specify that their effects last until the powers are dispelled or destroyed.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Instantaneous</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">Many powers are instantaneous. The power harms, heals, creates, or alters a creature or an object in a way that can’t be dispelled, because its effect exists only for an instant.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Concentration</font><font face="sans-serif">\n"   "Some powers require you to maintain concentration in order to keep their effect active. If you lose concentration, such a power ends.\n\n"   "If a power must be maintained with concentration, that fact appears in its Duration entry, and the power specifies how long you can concentrate on it. You can end concentration at any time (no action required).\n\n"   "Normal activity, such as moving and attacking, doesn’t interfere with concentration. The following factors can break concentration\n\n" •  "<b>Casting another power that requires concentration:</b> You lose concentration on a power if you cast another power that requires concentration. You can’t concentrate on two powers at once.\n" •  "<b>Taking damage:</b> Whenever you take damage while you are concentrating on a power, you must make a Constitution saving throw to maintain your concentration. The DC equals 10 or half the damage you take, whichever number is higher. If you take damage from multiple sources, such as a blaster shot and a force power, you make a separate saving throw for each source of damage.\n" •  "<b>Being incapacitated or killed:</b> You lose concentration on a power if you are incapacitated or if you die.\n"   "The GM might also decide that certain environmental phenomena, such as turbulence on a ship or rocky terrain on a speeder, require you to succeed on a DC 10 Constitution saving throw to maintain concentration on a power.</font>\n</item>
        <item name="info_14_Header">targets</item>
        <item name="info_14_Text"><font face="sans-serif">A typical power requires you to pick one or more targets to be affected by the power’s effect. A power’s description tells you whether the power targets creatures, objects, or a point of origin for an area of effect (described below). Unless a power has a perceptible effect, a creature might not know it was targeted by a power at all. An effect like crackling lightning is obvious, but a more subtle effect, such as an attempt to read a creature’s thoughts, typically goes unnoticed, unless a power says otherwise.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">A Clear Path to the Target</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">To target something, you must have a clear path to it, so it can’t be behind total cover.\n\n"   "If you place an area of effect at a point that you can’t see and an obstruction, such as a wall, is between you and that point, the point of origin comes into being on the near side of that obstruction.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Targeting Yourself</font><font face="sans-serif">\n"   "If a power targets a creature of your choice, you can choose yourself, unless the creature must be hostile or specifically a creature other than you. If you are in the area of effect of a power you cast, you can target yourself.</font>\n</item>
        <item name="info_15_Header">areas of effect</item>
        <item name="info_15_Text"><font face="sans-serif">Powers such as force storm and explosion cover an area, allowing them to affect multiple creatures at once.\n\n"   "A power’s description specifies its area of effect, which typically has one of five different shapes: cone, cube, cylinder, line, or sphere. Every area of effect has a point of origin, a location from which the power’s effect erupts. The rules for each shape specify how you position its point of origin. Typically, a point of origin is a point in space, but some powers have an area whose origin is a creature or an object.\n\n"   "A power’s effect expands in straight lines from the point of origin. If no unblocked straight line extends from the point of origin to a location within the area of effect, that location isn’t included in the power’s area. To block one of these imaginary lines, an obstruction must provide total cover, as explained in chapter 9.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Cone</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">A cone extends in a direction you choose from its point of origin. A cone’s width at a given point along its length is equal to that points distance from the point of origin. A cone’s area of effect specifies its maximum length.\n\n"   "A cone’s point of origin is not included in the cones area of effect, unless you decide otherwise.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Cube</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">You select a cube’s point of origin, which lies anywhere on a face of the cubic effect. The cube’s size is expressed as the length of each side.\n\n"   "A cube’s point of origin is not included in the cube’s area of effect, unless you decide otherwise.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Cylinder</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">A cylinder’s point of origin is the center of a circle of a particular radius, as given in the power description. The circle must either be on the ground or at the height of the power effect. The energy in a cylinder expands in straight lines from the point of origin to the perimeter of the circle, forming the base of the cylinder. The power’s effect then shoots up from the base or down from the top, to a distance equal to the height of the cylinder.\n\n"   "A cylinder’s point of origin is included in the cylinder’s area of effect.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Line</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">A line extends from its point of origin in a straight path up to its length and covers an area defined by its width. A line’s point of origin is not included in the line’s area of effect, unless you decide otherwise.</font>
            \n\n<font size="22">Sphere</font>\n"   "<font face="sans-serif">You select a sphere’s point of origin, and the sphere extends outward from that point. The sphere’s size is expressed as a radius in feet that extends from the point.\n\n"   "A sphere’s point of origin is included in the sphere’s area of effect.</font>\n</item>
        <item name="info_16_Header">saving throws</item>
        <item name="info_16_Text">Many powers specify that a target can make a saving throw to avoid some or all of a power’s effects. The power specifies the ability that the target uses for the save and what happens on a success or failure.\n\n"   "The DC to resist one of your powers equals 8 + your force- or tech-casting ability modifier + your proficiency bonus + any special modifiers.\n</item>
        <item name="info_17_Header">attack rolls</item>
        <item name="info_17_Text">Some powers require the caster to make an attack roll to determine whether the power effect hits the intended target. Your attack bonus with a power attack equals your force- or tech-casting ability modifier + your proficiency bonus. Most powers that require attack rolls involve ranged attacks. Remember that you have disadvantage on a ranged attack roll if you are within 5 feet of a hostile creature that can see you and that isn’t incapacitated (see chapter 9).>\n</item>
        <item name="info_18_Header">combining effects</item>
        <item name="info_18_Text">The effects of different powers add together while the durations of those powers overlap. The effects of the same power cast multiple times-or identical effects from separate powers-don’t combine, however. Instead, the most potent effect~such as the highest bonus-from those castings applies while their durations overlap.\n\n"   "For example, if two consulars cast guidance on the same target, that character gains the power’s benefit only once; he or she doesn’t get to roll two bonus dice. Alternatively, if a character is targeted by both knight speed and tactical advantage, they only gain the benefits once.\n</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>