<resources>

    <!--Forcecasting-->

    <!--Sorts , Dark/Light-->
    <string name="sortABCdown"><font color="#D4af37">ABC <font size="21"><b>↓</b></font></font></string>
    <string name="sortABCup"><font color="#D4af37">ABC <font size="21"><b>↑</b></font></font></string>
    <string name="sortLvldown"><font color="#D4af37">LvL <font size="21"><b>↓</b></font></font></string>
    <string name="sortLvlup"><font color="#D4af37">LvL <font size="21"><b>↑</b></font></font></string>
    <string name="Dark"><font color="red">Dark</font></string>
    <string name="Light"><font color="cyan">Light</font></string>
    <string name="All"><font color="#D4af37">All</font></string>

    <!--Extra needed for Force powers-->
    <string name="insanity2"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif">\n"    "At the end of each of its turns, an affected target can make a Wisdom saving throw. If it succeeds, this effect ends for that target.\n<b>"    "Force Potency:</b>When you cast this power using a power slot of 6th level or higher, the radius of the sphere increases by 5 feet for each force slot level above 5th.</font></font></string>
    <string name="insanitytable1"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif">The creature uses all its movement to move in a\nrandom direction. To determine the direction, roll a d8\nand assign a direction to each die face. The creature\ndoesn\'t take an action this turn.</font></font></string>
    <string name="insanitytable2"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif">The creature doesn\'t move or take actions this turn.</font></font></string>
    <string name="insanitytable3"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif">The creature uses its action to make a melee attack\nagainst a randomly determined creature within its\nreach. If there is no creature within its reach, the\ncreature does nothing this turn.</font></font></string>

    <string name="mass_animation2"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif"><b>"    "Force Potency:</b>If you cast this power using a force slot of 6th level or higher, you can animate two additional objects for each slot level above 5th.</font></font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationHeader1"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif"><b>Size</b></font></font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationHeader2"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif"><b>HP</b></font></font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationHeader3"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif"><b>AC</b></font></font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationHeader4"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif"><b>Attack</b></font></font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable1_1"><font size="18">Tiny</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable1_2"><font size="18">20</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable1_3"><font size="18">16</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable1_4"><font size="18">+6 to hit, 1d4 + 3 damage</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable2_1"><font size="18">Small</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable2_2"><font size="18">25</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable2_3"><font size="18">15</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable2_4"><font size="18">+6 to hit, 1d8 + 2 damage</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable3_1"><font size="18">Medium</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable3_2"><font size="18">40</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable3_3"><font size="18">13</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable3_4"><font size="18">+5 to hit, 2d6 + 1 damage</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable4_1"><font size="18">Large</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable4_2"><font size="18">50</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable4_3"><font size="18">10</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable4_4"><font size="18">+6 to hit, 2d10 + 2 damage</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable5_1"><font size="18">Huge</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable5_2"><font size="18">80</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable5_3"><font size="18">10</font></string>
    <string name="mass_animationtable5_4"><font size="18">+8 to hit, 2d12 + 4 damage</font></string>
    <!--utility stuff for ForceCasting-->
    <string name="one"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif">1</font></font></string>
    <string name="twotosix"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif">2-6</font></font></string>
    <string name="seventoeight"><font size="18"><font face="sans-serif">7-8</font></font></string>
    <string name="at_will">At Will</string>
    <string name="first_level">1st-Level</string>
    <string name="second_level">2nd-Level</string>
    <string name="third_level">3rd-Level</string>
    <string name="fourth_level">4th-Level</string>
    <string name="fifth_level">5th-Level</string>
    <string name="sixth_level">6th-Level</string>
    <string name="seventh_level">7th-Level</string>
    <string name="eighth_level">8th-Level</string>
    <string name="nineth_level">9th-Level</string>
    <string name="forcepowers">forcepowers</string>
    <string name="force">FoXcE</string>
    <string name="favorites_forcepowers"><font color="#D4af37">Favorites</font></string>

    <!--Classes -->

    <!--Berserker -->
    <string name="berserker">BEXSEXKEX</string>
    <string name="berserkerinstincts">Berserker\nInstincts</string>
    <string name="instincts"><font color="#D4af37">Instincts</font></string>
    <string name="berserker_instinctsHeader">berserker instincts</string>
    <string name="berserker_instinctstext"><font face="sans-serif">the instincts are presented in alphabetical order.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nacklay\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nwhile raging, you have advantage on constitution saving throws.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nbantha\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>prerequisite</b>: 7th level \nyour carrying capacity and the weight you can push, drag, or lift doubles. if it would already double, it instead triples. additionally, you have advantage on strength checks made to push, pull, lift, or break objects.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nblurrg\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nwhether mounted or on foot, your travel pace is doubled, as is the travel pace of up to ten companions while they\'re within 60 feet of you and you\'re not incapacitated.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nboggdo\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>prerequisite</b>: 13th level\nwhile raging you have a flying speed equal to your current walking speed, though you fall if you end your turn in the air and nothing else is holding you aloft.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nchirodactyl\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>prerequisite</b>: 7th level\nwhile raging, you have blindsight to a range of 30 feet, and you have advantage on wisdom (perception) checks that rely on sound, as long as you aren\'t deafened.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\ndewback\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nchoose three damage types other than true damage. while raging, you have resistance to the chosen damage types.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nfighter\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nyou adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. choose one of the fighting style options, detailed in chapter 6.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nfyrnock\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nwhile raging, you can use your bonus action to leap up to 30 feet to an empty space you can see. when you land you deal kinetic damage equal to your strength modifier to each creature within 5 feet of where you land. you can use this feature twice. you gain an additional use at 5th, 9th, 13th, and 17th level. you regain all expended uses when you complete a long rest.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nhawk\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>prerequisite</b>: 7th level\n you can see up to 1 mile away with no difficulty. you are able to discern even fine details as though looking at something no more than 100 feet away from you. additionally, dim light doesn\'t impose disadvantage on your wisdom (perception) checks.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nkatarn\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nyou gain a climbing speed equal to your movement speed.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nloth-cat\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nwhile you\'re raging, other creatures have disadvantage on opportunity attack rolls against you, and you can take the dash action as a bonus action on your turn.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\npredator\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nyour speed increases by 10 feet.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nrancor\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>prerequisite</b>: 13th level\nwhile you\'re raging any creature within 5 feet of you that\'s hostile to you has disadvantage on attack rolls against targets other than you or another character with this feature. an enemy is immune to this effect if it can\'t see or hear you or if it can\'t be frightened.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\ntactician\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\nwhen you use your reckless attack feature, you can choose to not have advantage on your attack rolls this turn. if you do so, friendly creatures within 5 feet of a hostile creature that is within 5 feet of you have advantage on attack rolls against that creature.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\ntracker\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>prerequisite</b>: 7th level\nyou can track other creatures while traveling at a fast pace, and you can move stealthily while traveling at a normal pace.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nterentatek\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>prerequisite</b>: 13th level\nwhen you are forced to make a saving throw against a force power, you can immediately use your reaction to move up to half your speed towards the source power\'s caster. if you end this movement within 5 feet of the target, you can immediately make one melee weapon attack against the target as a part of that reaction.\n</font>
    <font size="24">\nvaractyl\'s instinct</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>prerequisite</b>: 13th level\nwhile raging, you have advantage on dexterity checks, your attack rolls can\'t suffer from disadvantage, and each slowed level only reduces your speed by 5 feet, unless it would reduce your speed to 0.</font></string>
    <string name="the_berserker">The Berserker</string>
    <string name="rages">Rages</string>
    <string name="ragedamage">Rage\nDamage</string>
    <string name="ballistic_approach"><font color="#D4af37">Ballistic Approach</font></string>
    <string name="cyclone_approach"><font color="#D4af37">Cyclone Approach</font></string>
    <string name="juggernaut_approach"><font color="#D4af37">Juggernaut Approach</font></string>
    <string name="marauder_approach"><font color="#D4af37">Marauder Approach</font></string>
    <string name="marauder_forcecasting">Marauder Forcecasting</string>

    <!--Consular -->
    <string name="consular">conSuLAX</string>
    <string name="the_consular">The coNSuLAX</string>
    <string name="way_of_balance"><font color="#D4af37">Way of Balance</font></string>
    <string name="way_of_lightning"><font color="#D4af37">Way of Lightning</font></string>
    <string name="way_of_the_sage"><font color="#D4af37">Way of the Sage</font></string>
    <string name="way_of_suggestion"><font color="#D4af37">Way of Suggestion</font></string>
    <string name="consular_force_empowered_castings"><font color="#D4af37"><font size="13">Force\nEmpowered\nCastings</font></font></string>
    <string name="consular_force_empowered_castingsHeader">Force Empowered Castings</string>
    <string name="force_empowered_casting_options">Force-Empowered\nCasting Options</string>
    <string name="consular_force_empowered_castingstext"><font face="sans-serif">the castings are presented in alphabetical order."  "\n</font>
            <font size="24">\ncareful power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you cast a power that forces other creatures to make a saving throw, you can protect some of those creatures from the power\'s full force. To do so, you spend 1 additional force point and choose a number of those creatures up to your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice, minimum of one). A chosen creature automatically succeeds on its saving throw against the power.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nDistant power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you cast a power that has a range of 5 feet or greater, you can spend 1 additional force point to double the range of the power.\n"    "Alternatively, when you cast a power that has a range of touch, you can spend 1 additional force point to make the range of the power 30 feet.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nExtended power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you cast a power that has a duration of 1 minute or longer, you can spend 1 additional force point to double its duration, to a maximum duration of 24 hours.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nHeightened power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you cast a power that forces a creature to make a saving throw to resist its effects, you can spend 3 additional force points to give one target of the power disadvantage on its first saving throw made against the power.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nImproved power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you roll damage for a power, you can spend 1 additional force point to reroll a number of the damage dice up to your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice, minimum of one). You must use the new rolls.\n"    "You can use Improved Power even if you have already used a different Force-Empowered Casting option during the casting of the power.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nLingering power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you cast a power that requires concentration to maintain you can choose to spend 3 additional force points. If you do, when you lose concentration on the power, the power will not end until the end of your next turn.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nPinpoint power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you cast a power that allows you to force creatures in an area to make a saving throw you can instead spend 1 force point and make a ranged force attack against a single target that would be in the range. On a hit the target suffers the effects as though they failed their saving throw.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nquickened power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you cast a power that has a casting time of 1 action, you can spend 2 additional force points to change the casting time to 1 bonus action for this casting.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nXefocused power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you are forced to make a Constitution saving throw to maintain concentration on a power you can use your reaction and spend 2 force points to automatically succeed on the saving throw.\n"    "You can use Refocused Power even if you have already used a different Force-Empowered Casting option during the casting of the power.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nSeeking power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nIf you miss with a force power that calls for an attack roll, you can spend 2 force points to reroll the attack. You must use the new roll.\n"    "You can use Seeking Power even if you have already used a different Force-Empowered Casting option during the casting of the power.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\ntwinned power</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you cast a power that can only have one target and doesn\'t have a range of self, you can spend a number of additional force points equal to the power\'s level to choose a second target in range with the same power (1 force point if the power is at-will).</font></string>

    <!--Engineer-->
    <string name="engineer">ENGiNEEX</string>
    <string name="the_engineer">The ENGiNEEX</string>
    <string name="armormech_engineering"><font color="#D4af37">Armormech Engineering</font></string>
    <string name="armormech_modifications"><font color="#D4af37">Armormech Modifications</font></string>
    <string name="armormech_modificationsHeader">Armormech Modifications</string>
    <string name="armormech_modificationstext"><font face="sans-serif">the modifications are presented in alphabetical order.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAbsorption Shield</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Physical Shield\nYou modify your physical shield to block incoming damage. As a bonus action you can activate this ability and gain temporary hit points equal to 1d4 + Intelligence modifier, which last for one hour.\n"    "You can use this feature twice. You gain an additional use at 5th, 9th, 13th, and 17th level. You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAccelerated Movement</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nYou reduce the weight of your modified armor\'s bulk and increase the power to joints. If the armor has a Strength requirement, you ignore it. The modified armor\'s weight is reduced by 15 lbs. While wearing your modified armor your speed increases by 10 feet. This applies to all movement speeds you have while wearing your armor.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAdaptable Armor</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nYou integrate deployable hooks and fins into your armor, augmenting its mobility. While wearing your modified armor, you gain a climbing speed equal to your walking speed, and you can move up, down, and across vertical surfaces and upside down along ceilings, while leaving your hands free. Additionally, you gain a swim speed equal to your walking speed.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAdvanced Power Fist</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 11th level, Prototype Power Fist\nYou further modify your modified armor\'s gauntlet with increased reinforcement and weight. Your modified armor\'s unarmed strike deals 1d8 kinetic damage. Additionally, your critical hit range with your unarmed strikes increases by 1.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nArtificially intelligent</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Armor\You install an artificial intelligence into your modified armor. While wearing your modified armor, when you make an ability check, your armor\'s artificial intelligence can take the Help action.\n"    "You can use this feature four times. You gain an additional use at 13th and 17th level. You regain all expended uses when you complete a long rest.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nBonded Plates</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou gain a +1 bonus to AC against melee attacks. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\ncollapsible Suit</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Armor\nYour modified armor can collapse into a case for easy storage. When transformed this way the armor is indistinguishable from a normal case and weighs one-third its normal weight. As an action you can don or doff the armor, allowing it to transform as needed.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nDarkvision Armor</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nWhile wearing your modified armor, you have darkvision to a range of 60 feet. If you already have darkvision, this modification increases its range by 30 feet.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nEnhanced Endurance</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nWhen you are reduced to 0 hit points while wearing your modified armor but not killed outright, you can drop to 1 hit point instead. You can\'t use this feature again until you finish a long rest.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nElectroshock Shield</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Shield Generator\nYou install electroshockers in your shield generator. Whenever an enemy misses you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction to do 1d4 + your Intelligence modifier lightning damage to the attacker.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nFlight</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Armor\nYou integrate a propulsion system into your modified armor. While wearing your modified armor you have an enhanced flying speed of 30 feet.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nGrappling Harpoon</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nYour modified armor gains an integrated grappling harpoon set into your gauntlet. With this harpoon, you can make a ranged weapon attack with a range of 30/60. On a hit, it deals 1d6 kinetic damage. This attack can target a surface, object, or creature.\n"    "A creature struck by this attack is impaled by the harpoon. As an action, a creature can attempt to remove the harpoon. Removing the harpoon requires a Strength check. While the harpoon is stuck in the target, you are connected to the target by a 60 foot cable.\n"    "While the harpoon is deployed, you can use your bonus action to activate the reel, pulling yourself to the location if the target is larger than you. A creature or object your size or smaller is pulled to you. Alternatively, you can opt to release the cable (no action required).\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you can\'t use it again until you recover and reinsert the harpoon as an action.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nHeavy Suit</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Armor\nYou enhance your suit, making it difficult to move. As a bonus action, you can anchor or deanchor your feet to the ground. While anchored, your speed is 0, you have advantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws, and your carrying capacity and the weight you can push, drag, or lift doubles. If it would already double, it instead triples.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\ninfiltration Suit</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nYou install a cloaking device in your modified armor. This device has 2 charges. As an action you can use 1 charge to cast infiltrate targeting yourself.\n"    "The cloaking device regains all expended charges after a long rest.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nMagnetized Shield</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Physical Shield\nYou modify your physical shield such that when a melee weapon attack misses you by an amount less than or equal to your bonus to AC from your shield, the attacking creature must make a Strength check against your tech save DC. On a failed save, the creature\'s weapon adheres to the shield. As an action, a creature can repeat this check. On a success, the weapon is freed.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\noverload Shield</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Shield Generator\nYou modify your shield generator to overload. As an action you can overload your shield. Each Large or smaller creature within 5 feet of you must make a Dexterity or Strength saving throw (their choice). On a failed save, they are pushed back 5 feet and knocked prone.\n"    "You can use this feature twice. You gain an additional use at 5th, 9th, 13th, and 17th level. You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nPower Fist</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nYou modify your modified armor gauntlet with increased reinforcement and weight. Your modified armor\'s unarmed strike deals 1d4 kinetic damage.\n"    "Additionally, when you take the Attack action and make an unarmed strike, you can make an additional unarmed strike as a bonus action.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nPrototype Power Fist</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Power Fist\nYou further modify your modified armor gauntlet with increased reinforcement and weight. Your modified armor\'s unarmed strike deals 1d6 kinetic damage and has the following property.\n"    "If you or your target move at least 10 feet in a straight line immediately before making an unarmed strike, the first unarmed strike you make deals additional damage equal to your Intelligence modifier.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nXeinforced underlay</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou gain a +1 bonus to AC against ranged attacks. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nXesistance</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nYou tune your modified armor against certain forms of damage. Choose acid, cold, fire, ion, lightning, or sonic damage. While wearing your modified armor you have resistance to that type of damage.\n"    "You can select this modification multiple times. Each time you do so, you must choose a different damage type.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nSealed Suit</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Armor\nAs a bonus action you can hermetically seal your modified armor, giving you an air supply for up to 1 hour and making you immune to poison (but not curing you of existing poisoned conditions). Your armor regains 1 minute of air for every minute that you are not submerged and the armor is not sealed.\n"    "Additionally, while you are wearing your modified armor you are considered adapted to cold and hot climates as well as high altitude, as described in chapter 5 of the Dungeon Master\'s Guide.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nSentient Armor</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 13th level, Artificially Intelligent\nYour artificial intelligence has learned to control the suit without you being in it. It is now a valid target of the tracker droid interface tech power.\n"    "While your armor is acting independently, it uses your ability scores, saving throws, and skills, and it has hit points equal to your engineer level. If reduced to 0 hit points, it falls directly to the ground, and it can not be equipped again until you finish a long rest.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nShield Amplifier</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Shield Generator\nYou modify your shield generator to project outward. As a bonus action you can amplify your shield until the start of your next turn. Each creature within 5 feet of you gains a bonus to AC equal to your shield\'s bonus.\n"    "You can use this feature twice. You gain an additional use at 5th, 9th, 13th, and 17th level. You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nShield Anchor</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Physical Shield\nYou modify your shield to be used as a portable source of cover. As an action, you can anchor or deanchor the shield. While anchored, you gain no benefit from a shield, and it does not require the use of a hand. Instead, while anchored, a light shield provides one-quarter cover, a medium shield provides half cover, and a heavy shield provides three-quarters cover.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nTech Blast</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nYou modify your modified armor gauntlet with a blaster weapon with which you are proficient. The weapon uses your Intelligence modifier for its attack and damage rolls, and deals 1d8 energy damage on a hit. It has a normal range of 30 feet and a long range of 120 feet.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nWeapon Integration Armoring</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Armor\nYou can integrate a single weapon that weighs no more than 8 lb. into your armor. While integrated, that weapon gains the hidden property. Additionally, you have advantage on Strength saving throws to avoid being disarmed.\n</font></string>
    <string name="armstech_engineering"><font color="#D4af37">Armstech Engineering</font></string>
    <string name="armstech_modifications"><font color="#D4af37">Armstech Modifications</font></string>
    <string name="armstech_modificationsHeader">Armstech Modifications</string>
    <string name="armstech_modificationstext"><font face="sans-serif">the modifications are presented in alphabetical order.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nAccuracy Focus</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Blaster\nYou gain a +1 bonus to attack rolls made with this weapon. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nAmplifying Barrel</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Blaster\nYou gain a +1 bonus to damage rolls made with this weapon. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nBayonet</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Blaster\nYou affix a short blade to the barrel of your modified blaster weapon, allowing you to make a melee weapon attack with it. The blade is a vibroweapon weapon with the finesse property that you are proficient with, and deals 1d6 kinetic damage.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nBurst core</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Blaster\nYour weapon gains the burst property, with a burst number equal to its reload number.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nBooming Strikes</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou pack extra power into your modified weapon. Once per turn, when you hit with the weapon, you can deal an additional 1d6 damage. If you do so, the weapon makes a loud boom which can be heard 100 feet away. If you are hidden, Intelligence (Investigation) and Wisdom (Perception) checks made to locate you that rely on sound have advantage.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\ncelerity oscillator</font><font face="sans-serif">\nOnce per turn, when you deal damage with your modified weapon, your walking speed increases by 10 feet until the start of your next turn, and the damaged creature can\'t make opportunity attacks against you for the rest of your turn.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\ncollapsible Frame</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Vibroweapon\nYou install an expandable hilt on your modified weapon. Your modified weapon gains the reach property.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\ncompensation oscillator</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Vibroweapon with the dexterity property\nYou install a compensation oscillator in your modified vibroweapon, removing the dexterity property from it.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\ncontoured grip</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Vibroweapon\nYou gain a +1 bonus to attack rolls made with this weapon. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nExpanded Magazine</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Blaster\nYour modified weapon can be more efficiently reloaded. You can reload your modified weapon once without using an action. You can\'t use this feature again until you reload the weapon with an action.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nFlashlight</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou affix a targeted light to your weapon. As a bonus action, you can toggle the light on or off. While on, your weapon sheds bright light in a 60-foot cone.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nHarpoon Xeel</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou install a secondary firemode that launches a harpoon attached to a tightly coiled cord. With this harpoon, you can make a ranged weapon attack with a range of 30/60. On a hit, it deals 1d6 kinetic damage. This attack can target a surface, object, or creature.\n"    "A creature struck by this attack is impaled by the harpoon. As an action, a creature can attempt to remove the harpoon. Removing the harpoon requires a Strength check. While the harpoon is stuck in the target, you are connected to the target by a 60 foot cable.\n"    "While connected in this manner, you can use your bonus action to activate the reel, pulling yourself to the location if the target is your size or larger. A creature or object smaller than you is pulled to you. Alternatively, you can opt to release the cable (no action required).\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you can\'t use it again until you recover and reinsert the harpoon as an action.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nimbue Weapon</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level\nYou modify your weapon to carry a charge. Over the course of a short rest, you can cast an at-will tech power, channeling it into your weapon. The next time you hit with your weapon, the stored power is released. If the power would require an attack roll, make a tech attack roll. If the power would require a saving throw, the target must make the saving throw as normal. On a hit, or a failure, the target suffers the power\'s normal effects.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nimproved Burst core</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Burst Core\nYour weapon\'s burst number is reduced to half its reload number.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nintegrated magazine</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Expanded Magazine\nYour modified weapon can be more efficiently reloaded. You can reload your modified weapon twice without using an action. You can\'t use this feature again until you reload the weapon with an action.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\njagged oscillator</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Vibroweapon\nWhen you critically hit with the weapon, you deal an additional 1d8 kinetic damage.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nKeen oscillator</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Jagged Oscillator\nYour weapon\'s critical hit range increases by 1.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nNeutronium Edge</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Vibroweapon\nYou gain a +1 bonus to damage rolls made with this weapon. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\novercharge Weapon</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 11th level, Booming Strikes\nYou gain the ability to channel your tech power to enhance your weapon\'s damage. You can expend one tech slot to deal additional damage to the target. The extra damage is 1d6 for a 1st-level tech slot, plus 1d6 for each slot level higher than 1st, to a maximum of 5d6. The damage is the same type as the weapon damage. If you also use your Booming Strikes with an attack, you add this damage to the extra damage of your Booming Strikes.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nPower Loop</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level\nWhen you hit with the weapon, you can choose to channel the energy generated, gaining temporary hit points equal to half the damage dealt.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a long rest before you can use it again.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nXecoil Dampener</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Blaster with the strength property\nYou install a recoil dampener in your modified blaster, removing the strength property from it.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nXeturning Weapon Guard</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Vibroweapon\nYou install a retractible chain in your modified vibroweapon. If the weapon does not already have the thrown property, it gains it with a range of 20/60. Additionally, it gains the returning property.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nScreening Weapon</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou modify your modified weapon with a sound dampening module. When you make a weapon attack with your weapon while hidden, Investigation and Perception checks made to locate you that rely on sound have disadvantage.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nShock Absorber</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou add a reclamation device to your modified weapon to gather energy from the surroundings when it is present. While wielding your modified weapon, you can cast the absorb energy tech power and the power\'s extra damage applies to both melee and ranged weapon attacks.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nSiege Weapon</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou modify your weapon to be more effective against barriers. Your weapon deals double damage against structures.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nShocking Harpoon</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Harpoon Reel\nAfter hitting a creature with the harpoon fire mode, you can use the connection to deliver an at-will tech power. As a bonus action, you can cast an at-will tech power at the target with a range of touch. If the power requires an attack roll, you have advantage. If the target requires a saving throw, the target has disadvantage.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you can\'t use it again until you recover the harpoon.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nShocking oscillator</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Vibroweapon\nWhen you hit with the weapon, you can create an electronic burst. Each creature in a 15-foot cone centered on the creature you hit must make a Dexterity saving throw, taking 1d8 lightning damage on a failed save or half as much on a successful one.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a long rest before you can use it again.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nSnap Fire</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Blaster\nYou modify your modified blaster weapon for quick shots. You can use your reaction to take a opportunity attack with your modified weapon if an enemy comes within 10 feet of you. You have disadvantage on this attack.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nStaggering oscillator</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Vibroweapon\nWhen you hit with the weapon, you can force the target to make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save, the creature is pushed back 10 feet and knocked prone.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a short or long rest before you can use it again.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nTracker</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou add a tracking mechanism to your modified weapon. The tracker has 3 charges. As a bonus action you can use 1 charge to cast target lock. As an action you can use 2 charges to cast detect invisibility.\n"    "The tracker regains all expended charges after a long rest.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nTrueLight</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 11th level, Flashlight\nYou modify your flashlight with a toggle allowing you to briefly gain enhanced sight. As a bonus action, you can activate the truesight feature of your flashlight. When toggled on, for the next minute your flashlight now automatically dispel illusions and can detect invisibility, as with truesight.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a short or long rest before you can use it again.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvenomous oscillator</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Vibroweapon\nAs a bonus action, you can coat your weapon in a thin layer of poison for 1 minute. The next time you hit with the weapon, the creature must make a Constitution saving throw against your tech save DC. On a failed save, a creature takes 1d10 poison damage and becomes poisoned for 1 minute.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a long rest before you can use it again.\n</font></string>
    <string name="gadgeteer_engineering"><font color="#D4af37">Gadgeteer Engineering</font></string>
    <string name="gadgeteer_modifications"><font color="#D4af37">Gadgeteer Modifications</font></string>
    <string name="gadgeteer_modificationsHeader">Gadgeteer Modifications</string>
    <string name="gadgeteer_modificationstext"><font face="sans-serif">the modifications are presented in alphabetical order.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nAdvanced Ground System</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 13th level, Prototype Grounding System\nWhile wearing your gadgeteer harness you have immunity to lightning damage.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nAuto-injection Xegenerator</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou install a special kolto injector into your gadgeteer harness that can inject you with kolto in response to pain. When you take damage, you can use your reaction and expend a Hit Die to regain health as long as the damage would not reduce your hit points to 0.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nAutothrusters</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> Jet Pack\nYou can take the Dash and Disengage actions as a bonus action while your jet pack is active.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nclimbing Gloves</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> You craft a set of gloves with a powerful assisted grip. While wearing these gloves, you have a climbing speed of 20 feet, and you have advantage on Strength saving throws and Strength (Athletics) checks that involve climbing.\n\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nDarkvision Goggles</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou craft a pair of sight-enhancing goggles. While wearing these goggles, you have darkvision to a range of 60 feet. If you already have darkvision, this modification increases its range by 30 feet.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nExtended Tank</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Jet Pack\nYour jet pack now lasts up to 10 minutes when activated.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nFlame vents</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Jet Pack\nYou learn the flame sweep tech power and can cast it at first level without using tech points. Once you have used this ability, you cannot use it again until you finish a short or long rest.\n"    "Additionally, while your jet pack is active, you can cast flame sweep using your bonus action instead of your action.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nFrailcasting inhibitor</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou gain a +1 bonus to the tech save DC of powers you cast that requires a Strength or Constitution saving throw. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nGrounding System</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhile wearing your gadgeteer harness you are immune to the shocked condition.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nintegrated Amplifier</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou gain a +1 bonus to melee tech attack rolls. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nintegrated Xangefinder</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou gain a +1 bonus to ranged tech attack rolls. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nintelligence core override</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level\nYou can cast the override interface tech power at 5th level without spending tech points.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a long rest before you can use it again.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\njet Pack</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou integrate a jet pack into your gadgeteer harness to grant you temporary, limited flight. Activating or deactivating the jets requires a bonus action and, while active, you have a flying speed of 30 feet.\n"    "The jet pack last for 1 minute before deactivating. Once the jets have been activated, they can\'t be activated again until you finish a short or long rest.\n"    "Your jet pack\'s speed increases to 40 feet at 5th level, 50 feet at 9th level, 60 feet at 13th level, 70 feet at 17th level, and 80 feet at 20th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nMechanical Arm</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou create a mechanical arm which mounts to your shoulder, which you can use independently. You can only gain the benefit of items held by two of your arms at any given time.\n"    "You can choose this modification twice.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nMimicker</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level\nYou create a device that attaches to your gadgeteer harness. Your mimicker casts a shadow that makes you appear to be standing in a place near your actual location, causing any creature to have disadvantage on attack rolls against you. If you take damage, the property ceases to function for 1 minute. Your mimicker is suppressed while you are incapacitated, restrained, or otherwise unable to move.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nMiniaturized Hydraulics</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYour gadgeteer harness can store 20 pounds of equipment without adding to your encumbrance.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\noil Spill</font><font face="sans-serif">\nAs an action, you can cast the oil slick tech power without expending tech points. When you cast the power in this way, the oil will remain in place for the full duration of the power.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a short or long rest before you can use it again.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nPowered Grappling Hook</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Wrist-Mounted Grappling Hook\nWhile your wrist-mounted grappling hook is deployed, when you cast a tech power with a range of touch, your hook can deliver the power as if it had cast it.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nPrototype Ground System</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Grounding System\nWhile wearing your gadgeteer harness you have resistance to lightning damage.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nXendcasting inhibitor</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou gain a +1 bonus to the tech save DC of powers you cast that requires a Dexterity or Intelligence saving throw. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nquick Start Engine</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level, Jet Pack\nYou can now activate your Jet Pack as an object interaction rather than as a bonus action.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nXecycled Adrenals</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can augment a single adrenal to regain its charge. This adrenal can only be used by you, and it can only affect you. Once you\'ve used this adrenal, you can\'t use it again until you finish a long rest.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nXecycled Explosives</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can augment a single explosive to regain its charge. This explosive can only be used by you, and it uses your tech save DC instead of its own, unless its own DC would be higher. Once you\'ve used this explosive, you can\'t use it again until you finish a long rest.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nXecycled Stimpacs</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can augment a single stimpac to regain its charge. This stimpac can only be used by you, and it can only affect you. Once you\'ve used this stimpac, you can\'t use it again until you finish a long rest.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nSentry Turret</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou learn how to craft small sentry turrets shaped like globes that can adhere to any surface. As an action or bonus action (your choice), you can throw a sentry to a point you can see within range (30 feet + your Strength modifier x 5). At the end of each of your turns, a deployed sentry automatically targets a hostile creature within 10 feet of it. If multiple targets are available, one is chosen at random. The target must make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, it takes 1d4 energy damage and gains 1 slowed level until the end of your next turn. If a creature would be targeted by more than one of these sentries, it only makes this saving throw once, taking an additional d4 damage for each sentry beyond the first.\n"    "The sentries have 1 hit point, an armor class of 10, and can be repaired over the course of a long rest. Each sentry lasts for 1 minute before deactivating. You can maintain a number of sentries equal to your Intelligence modifier. Once a sentry has been activated, it can\'t be activated again until you finish a short or long rest.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nShocking Hook</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level, Wrist-Mounted Grappling Hook\nAfter hitting a creature with your grappling hook, you can use the connection to deliver an at-will tech power. As a bonus action, you can cast an at-will tech power at the target with a range of touch. If the power requires an attack roll, you have advantage. If the target requires a saving throw, the target has disadvantage.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you can\'t use it again until you recover the hook.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nStealth Field Generator</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 9th level\nYou create an augmented belt that functions as a portable, personal cloaking device. Activating or deactivating the generator requires a bonus action and, while active, you have advantage on Dexterity (Stealth) ability checks that rely on sight. The generator lasts for 1 minute. This effect ends early if you make an attack or cast a force- or tech- power.\n"    "Once the belt has been activated, it can\'t be activated again until you finish a short or long rest.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nShocking Barrier</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou enhanced your barriers. Whenever a creature with one of your barriers active takes damage from a creature within 5 feet of it, the damaged creature can roll your Potent Aptitude die, dealing the result of the die as lightning damage to the creature that damaged it.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nTruesight Goggles</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 11th level, Darkvision Goggles\nYou modify your goggles with a toggle allowing you to briefly gain enhanced sight. As a bonus action, you can activate the truesight feature of your goggles. When toggled on, for the next minute your goggles now automatically dispel illusions and can detect invisibility, as with truesight.\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a short or long rest before you can use it again.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nWeapon integration</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can integrate a single weapon that weighs no more than 8 lb. into your gadgeteer harness. While integrated, that weapon gains the hidden and fixed properties.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nWithercasting inhibitor</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 5th level\nYou gain a +1 bonus to the tech save DC of powers you cast that requires a Wisdom or Charisma saving throw. This bonus increases to +2 at 9th level and +3 at 13th level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nWrist-Mounted Grappling Hook</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou craft a wrist-mounted grappling hook weapon attached to a tightly coiled cord. With this contraption, you can make a ranged weapon attack with a range of 30/60. On a hit, it deals 1d4 kinetic damage. This attack can target a surface, object, or creature.\n"    "A creature struck by this attack is impaled by the hook. As an action, a creature can attempt to remove the hook. Removing the hook requires a Strength check. While the hook is stuck in the target, you are connected to the target by a 60 foot cable.\n"    "While the hook is deployed, you can use your bonus action to activate the reel, pulling yourself to the location if the target is your size or larger. A creature or object smaller than you is pulled to you. Alternatively, you can opt to release the cable (no action required).\n"    "Once you\'ve used this feature, you can\'t use it again until you recover and reinsert the hook as an action.\n</font></string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering"><font color="#D4af37">Unstable Engineering</font></string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_surge">uNSTABLE ENGiNEERiNG SuRGE</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_1">01"   "Roll on this table at the start of each of your turns for 1\n02"   "minute ignoring this result on subsequent rolls.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_2">03"   "For the next minute, you can see any invisible creature\n04"   "if you have line of sight to it.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_3">05"   "A DRK-1 tracker droid appears with 5 feet of you, then\n06"   "disappears 1 minute later.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_4">07"   "You cast <i>explosion</i> at 3rd-level centered on yourself\n08"   "without expending tech points.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_5">09"   "You cast <i>homing rockets</i> at 5th-level without expending\n10"   "tech points.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_6">11"   "Roll a d10. Your height changes by a number of inches\n12"   "equal to the roll: if odd, you shrink; if even, you grow.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_7">13"   "You fall asleep standing for 1 minute or until you take\n14"   "damage.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_8">15"   "For the next minute, you regain 5 hit points at the start\n16"   "of each of your turns</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_9">17"   "You grow a long beard made of feathers that remains\n18"   "until you sneeze.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_10">19"   "You cast <i>oil slick</i> centered on yourself without\n20"   "expending tech points</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_11">21"   "Creatures have disadvantage on the first saving throw\n22"   "they make against you in the next minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_12">23"   "Your skin turns a vibrant shade of blue. Any effect that\n24"   "ends a curse ends this.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_13">25"   "You grow an extra eye, granting advantage on Wisdom\n26"   "(Perception) checks that rely on sight for 1 minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_14">27"   "For the next minute, all your tech powers with a casting\n28"   "time of 1 action have a casting time of 1 bonus action.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_15">29"   "You teleport up to 60 feet to an unoccupied space of\n30"   "your choice that you can see.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_16">31"   "You take 2d10 lightning damage and are shocked for 1\n32"   "minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_17">33"   "Maximize the damage of the next damaging tech\n34"   "power you cast within the next minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_18">35"   "Roll a d10. Your age changes by a number of years\n36"   "equal to the roll: if odd, younger; if even, older.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_19">37"   "You start running uncontrollably for 1 minute, moving\n38"   "your entire speed each turn.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_20">39"   "You regain 2d10 hit points.\n40</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_21">41"   "Each creature within 30 feet of you is subjected to the\n42"   "<i>gleaming outline</i> tech power for 1 minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_22">43"   "For the next minute, you can teleport up to 20 feet as a\n44"   "bonus action on each of your turns.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_23">45"   "You are blinded and deafened for 1 minute.\n46</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_24">47"   "You have disadvantage on the first ability check, attack\n48"   "roll, or saving throw you make each turn for 1 minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_25">49"   "You can\'t speak for the next minute. Whenever you try,\n50"   "pink bubbles float out of your mouth.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_26">51"   "A shimmering energy barrier grants you a +2 bonus to\n52"   "AC for 1 minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_27">53"   "You are immune to being intoxicated by alcohol for\n54"   "the next 5d6 days.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_28">55"   "Your hair falls out but grows back within 24 hours. If\n56"   "you don\'t have hair, you instead grow it for 24 hours.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_29">57"   "For 1 minute, any flammable object not worn or\n58"   "carried you touch bursts into flame.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_30">59"   "You regain tech points equal to your Intelligence\n60"   "modifier (minimum of one).</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_31">61"   "For the next minute, you shout whenever you speak.\n62</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_32">63"   "You cast <i>smoke cloud</i> centered on yourself without\n64"   "expending tech points.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_33">65"   "Up to three creatures you choose within 30 feet of\n66"   "you take 4d10 lightning damage.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_34">67"   "You are frightened by the nearest creature until the\n68"   "end of your next turn.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_35">69"   "Each creature within 30 feet of you becomes invisible\n70"   "for 1 minute, or until it attacks or casts a power.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_36">71"   "You gain resistance to all damage for the next\n72"   "minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_37">73"   "A random creature within 60 feet of you becomes\n74"   "poisoned for 1d4 hours.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_38">75"   "You emit bright light in a 30-foot radius for 1 minute.\n76</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_39">77"   "Each creature within 30 feet of you except you gains\n78"   "the benefits of <i>mirror image</i> for 1 minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_40">79"   "Illusory butterflies and flower petals flutter in the air\n80"   "within 10 feet of you for the next minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_41">81"   "You can take one additional action immediately.\n82</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_42">83"   "Each creature within 30 feet of you takes 1d10 necrotic\n84"   "damage and you gain hit points equal to the damage.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_43">85"   "You cast <i>mirror image</i> without expending tech points.\n86</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_44">87"   "You are frozen in carbonite and paralyzed for 1 minute\n88"   "or until you take damage.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_45">89"   "You turn invisible and can\'t make sound for 1 minute\n90"   "or until you attack or cast a power.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_46">91"   "If you die within the next minute, you immediately\n92"   "come back to life as if by the <i>defibrillate</i> power.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_47">93"   "Your size increases by one size category for the next\n94"   "minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_48">95"   "You and all creatures within 30 feet of you gain\n96"   "vulnerability to energy damage for the next minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_49">97"   "You are surrounded by faint, ethereal music for the\n98"   "next minute.</string>
    <string name="unstable_engineering_table_50">99"   "You regain half your expended tech points.\n100</string>
    <string name="modification_slots">Modification\nSlots</string>

    <!--Fighter -->
    <string name="fighter">FiGHTEX</string>
    <string name="the_fighter">The FiGHTEX</string>
    <string name="fighter_strategies"><font color="#D4af37">Fighter Strategies</font></string>
    <string name="strategies_known">Strategies\nKnown</string>
    <string name="fighter_strategiesHeader">Fighter Strategies</string>
    <string name="fighter_strategiestext"><font face="sans-serif">the strategies are presented in alphabetical order.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\ncover Strategist</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou treat partial cover as one step higher (from onequarter to half or half to three-quarters). While in cover, your attacks reduce partial cover by one step (from three-quarters to half or half to one-quarter).\n</font>
            <font size="24">\ncunning Strategist</font><font face="sans-serif">\nChoose two from the following. You can perform each of the chosen options with your bonus action, instead of your action:\n\n•"   "Applying poison\n•"   "Dash\n•"   "Disengage\n•"   "Guard\n•"   "Help\n•"   "Hide\n•"   "Search\n•"   "Throwing grenades and setting mines\n•"   "While mounted on a controlled beast, having your beast make a single melee attack against a creature within its reach\n•"   "While mounted on a vehicle, taking a vehicle action (you can\'t take the same action twice in one turn)\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nEnduring Strategist</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou only need 3 hours of sleep during a long rest to gain its benefits, instead of 6. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it to gain its benefits. Lastly, you have advantage on saving throws against exhaustion.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nMastery Strategist</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou\'ve mastered a particular style of fighting. Choose one of the Fighting Mastery options, detailed in Chapter 6.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nLightweapon Strategist</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain proficiency in all lightweapons. Additionally, you no longer need the ability to cast force powers to learn features that grant lightsaber forms, and you learn one lightsaber form of your choice.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nManeuver Strategist</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou learn two additional maneuvers. When you complete a short rest, you can replace one of these maneuvers with another one. When you complete a long rest, you can replace both of these maneuvers with other ones.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nSkilled Strategist</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain proficiency in a skill and a tool, or two tools.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nStyle Strategist</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou adopt a second fighting style. Choose one of the fighting style options, detailed in Chapter 6. When you complete a long rest, you can change this style out for another one.\n</font></string>
    <string name="assault_specialist"><font color="#D4af37">Assault Specialist</font></string>
    <string name="blademaster_specialist"><font color="#D4af37">Blademaster Specialist</font></string>
    <string name="shield_specialist"><font color="#D4af37">Shield Specialist</font></string>
    <string name="shield_specialist_techcasting">Shield Specialist Techcasting</string>
    <string name="tactical_specialist"><font color="#D4af37">Tactical Specialist</font></string>
    <string name="maneuvers_known">Maneuvers\nKnown</string>
    <string name="superiority_dice_quantity">Superiority\nDice quantity</string>
    <string name="superiority_dice_size">Superiority\nDice Size</string>

    <!--Guardian-->
    <string name="guardian">GuAXDiAN</string>
    <string name="the_guardian">The GuAXDiAN</string>
    <string name="auras_known">Auras\nKnown</string>
    <string name="aura_radius">Aura\nRadius</string>
    <string name="guardian_auras"><font color="#D4af37">Guardian Auras</font></string>
    <string name="guardian_aurasHeader">Guardian Auras</string>
    <string name="guardian_aurastext"><font face="sans-serif">the auras are presented in alphabetical order. If multiple guardians grant the same aura, affected creatures can only benefit from it once. You must be conscious to grant the benefits of your auras.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAura of the conquest</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhenever a creature who is frightened of you starts its turn within 5 feet of you, its gains 4 slowed levels and takes psychic damage equal to half your guardian level.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAura of the conviction</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou and friendly creatures within 5 feet of you have advantage on saving throws against effects that would cause you to be charmed or frightened.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAura of the Hatred</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou and friendly creatures within 5 feet of you gain a bonus to the first melee weapon damage rolls you make each round equal to your Charisma modifier (minimum of +1).\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAura of the Presence</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhenever you or a friendly creature within 5 feet of you must make a saving throw, the creature can add your Wisdom modifier to the saving throw.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAura of the Protection</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhenever a creature within 5 feet of you takes damage, you can use your reaction to take that damage instead of that creature taking it. This feature doesn\'t transfer any other effects that might accompany the damage, and this damage can\'t be reduced in any way.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAura of the vigor</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhenever a friendly creature starts its turn within 5 feet of you, that creature gains temporary hit points equal to your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice, minimum of one).\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAura of the warding</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou and friendly creatures within 5 feet of you have resistance to damage from force powers.</font></string>
    <string name="makashi_form"><font color="#D4af37">Makashi Form</font></string>
    <string name="niman_form"><font color="#D4af37">Niman Form</font></string>
    <string name="shien_djem_so_form"><font color="#D4af37">Shien\/Djem So Form</font></string>
    <string name="soresu_form"><font color="#D4af37">Soresu Form</font></string>
    <string name="focused_strikes">Focused\nStrikes</string>

    <!--Monk-->
    <string name="monk">MoNK</string>
    <string name="the_monk">the MoNK</string>
    <string name="monastic_vows"><font color="#D4af37">Monastic Vows</font></string>
    <string name="monastic_vows_table">Monastic\nVows</string>
    <string name="monastic_vowsHeader">Monastic vows</string>
    <string name="monastic_vowstext"><font face="sans-serif">the vows are presented in alphabetical order.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of Deflection</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can use your reaction to divert a strike when you are dealt damage by a melee weapon attack. When you do so, the damage taken by the attack is reduced by 1d10 + your Dexterity modifier + your monk level.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the Devoted</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain a limited ability to manipulate the Force. See chapter 10 for the general rules of forcecasting and chapter 11 for the force powers list.\n</font>
            <font size="20">\nForce Powers known</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou learn 2 force powers of your choice. You learn an additional power at 3rd, 5th, 7th, 9th, 11th, 13th, 15th, and 17th level. You may not learn a force power of a level higher than your Max Power Level, and you may learn a force power at the same time you learn its prerequisite. You may only learn universal powers in this way.\n</font>
            <font size="20">\nForce Points</font><font face="sans-serif">\nRather than force points, powers you learn through this vow are cast using your focus points, at 1 focus point per power level. You may only cast universal powers in this way.\n</font>
            <font size="20">\nMax Power Level</font><font face="sans-serif">\nMany force powers can be overpowered, consuming more focus points to create a greater effect. You can overpower these abilities to a maximum level, which increases at higher levels. Your Max Power Level is 1st. It increases to 2nd at 7th level, 3rd at 13th level, and 4th at 17th level. You may only cast force powers at 4th-level once. You regain the ability to do so after a long rest.\n</font>
            <font size="20">\nForCecasting Ability</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou use your focus ability whenever a power refers to your forcecasting ability. If a power you cast with focus points calls for a saving throw, you use your focus save DC. If a power you cast with focus points calls for an attack roll, you use your focus attack modifier.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of Fate</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 7th level\nWhen you finish a short or long rest, roll a d20 and record the number rolled. Once before your next short or long rest, you can replace any attack roll, saving throw, or ability check made by you or a creature within 5 feet of you with this roll. You must choose to do so before the roll.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the Fighter</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the fighting Style options, detailed in Chapter 6.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the Focused</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can substitute Strength, Constitution, or Intelligence (chosen when you take this vow) for Wisdom or Charisma for your monk class features, except for other vows and Monastic Tradition features.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the Fortitude</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 7th level\nYou can use your action or bonus action to end one effect on yourself that is causing you to be blinded or deafened.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of Freedom</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou ignore unenhanced difficult terrain, and when you would use your action to break free of an effect that is grappling or restraining you, you can instead use your bonus action.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of intuition</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can no longer have disadvantage on attack rolls against creatures within 10 feet of you due to not being able to see them.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the Limber</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 7th level\nWhen you make your first unarmed strike on your turn, you can choose to spend 1 focus point. If you do so, your reach with your unarmed strikes increases by 5 feet until the end of your turn.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the Nemesis</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 13th level\nAs a bonus action, you can choose one creature within 30 feet that you can see. The creature must make a Wisdom saving throw against your focus save DC. On a successful save, the creature becomes immune to this feature for 24 hours. On a failed save, for the next minute, the creature has disadvantage on attack rolls against creatures other than you, and it must make an additional Wisdom saving throw each time it attempts to move to a space that is more than 30 feet away from you; if it succeeds on this saving throw, this feature doesn\'t restrict its movement for that turn.\n"    "This feature ends early if you attack another creature, if you target another hostile creature with a power or class feature, if a friendly creature damages the target, if a friendly creature targets it with a power or class feature, or if you target another creature with this feature.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the open Mind</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain proficiency in a skill of your choice. Additionally, you can spend 1 focus point and 10 minutes meditating on a skill in which you are proficient. If you do so, when you make an ability check with the chosen skill, you can add your Wisdom or Charisma modifier to the check. You can only have one instance of this feature active at a time.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of Precision</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 13th level\nYour critical hit range with unarmed strikes increases by 1.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of Xequital</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 13th level\nWhen you take the Dodge action and an attack made by a creature within 5 feet of you misses you before the start of your next turn, you can use your reaction to make one melee weapon attack with a monk weapon or unarmed strike against that creature.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of Xestoration</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you would make an unarmed strike, you can spend 1 focus point to instead touch a willing creature within your reach. Roll your Martial Arts die. The target gains hit points equal to the amount rolled + your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice, minimum of +1).\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the Sentry</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain proficiency in light and medium armor. Additionally, you can now gain the benefits of your Martial Arts and Unarmored Movement features while wearing light or medium armor as long as you are not wielding a shield.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of Serenity</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYour maximum focus increases by an amount equal to half your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice, minimum of +1).\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of Spirit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can use your choice of Wisdom or Charisma instead of Strength or Dexterity for the attack and damage rolls of your unarmed strikes and monk weapons. You must use the same modifier for both rolls.\n</font>
        <font size="24">\nvow of the versatile</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you would make an unarmed strike as part of your Martial Arts bonus action attack or your Flurry of Blows, you can instead make a weapon attack with a monk weapon you are wielding, using your Martial Arts die in place of the weapon\'s damage.\n</font></string>
    <string name="crimson_order"><font color="#D4af37">Crimson Order</font></string>
    <string name="echani_order"><font color="#D4af37">Echani Order</font></string>
    <string name="matukai_order"><font color="#D4af37">Matukai Order</font></string>
    <string name="nightsister_order"><font color="#D4af37">Nightsister Order</font></string>
    <string name="variant_monk"><b> Variant:Monk With Lightweapons</b>\n If monks gain lightweapon proficiency\n consider letting them use lightweapons as monk weapons\n provided the weapon lacks the dexterity, heavy, special\n and two-handed properties.</string>
    <string name="martial_arts">Martial\nArts</string>
    <string name="focus_points">Focus\nPoints</string>
    <string name="unarmored_movement">Unarmored\nMovement</string>

    <!--Operative-->
    <string name="operative">oPEXATivE</string>
    <string name="the_operative">the oPEXATivE</string>
    <string name="operative_exploits"><font color="#D4af37">Operative Exploits</font></string>
    <string name="operative_exploits_table">Operative\nExploits</string>
    <string name="operative_exploitsHeader">Operative Exploits</string>
    <string name="operative_exploitstext"><font face="sans-serif">the exploits are presented in alphabetical order.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\ncommander\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain proficiency in medium armor.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nExplorer\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou can hold your breath twice as long as you are normally able to, and take half as much damage from fall damage.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nFate\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 7th level\nWhen you finish a short or long rest, roll a d20 and record the number rolled. Once before your next short or long rest, you can replace any attack roll, saving throw, or ability check made by you or a creature within 5 feet of you with this roll. You must choose to do so before the roll.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nFighter\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the fighting Style options, detailed in Chapter 6.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nFreedom\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou ignore unenhanced difficult terrain, and when you would use your action to break free of an effect that is grappling or restraining you, you can instead use your bonus action.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nGuerrilla\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou only need 3 hours of sleep during a long rest to gain its benefits, instead of 6. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it to gain its benefits. Lastly, you have advantage on saving throws against exhaustion.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nLearner\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain proficiency in a skill and a tool, or two tools.\n"   " You can select this exploit multiple times, each time choosing a new skill and a tool, or two new tools.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nMentor\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\n<b>Prerequisite:</b> 13th level\nOnce per turn, whenever both you and a friendly creature within 60 feet that can see and hear you both have to make a saving throw to resist the same effect, you can choose to have disadvantage on the save. If you do so, the friendly creature gains advantage on the save. You can use this feature before or after you both make the saving throw, but you must do so before the GM says whether the save succeeds or fails.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nSkill\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou learn an exploit that enhances your ability to apply your knowledge to combat situations. You can take this exploit multiple times.\n"   " When you take the Attack action, you can use one of your skill exploits granted by this feature. You can use these features a combined two times. You gain an additional use at 5th, 9th, 13th, and 17th level. You regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.\n"   " Choose from the following. You must be proficient in the skill in order to take that skill\'s exploit.\n"   " <b>Aim (Stealth).</b> You attempt to line up a strike against a creature you can see that you are hidden from. Make a Dexterity (Stealth) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Perception) check. If your check succeeds, you gain a +10 bonus to the first attack roll you make against the target before the end of your next turn. If your check fails, you are no longer hidden from the target.\n"   " <b>Angle (Perception).</b> You attempt to predict the behavior of a humanoid you can see within 30 feet. Make a Wisdom (Perception) check contested by the target\'s Dexterity (Sleight of Hand) check. If your check succeeds, the first attack roll the target makes before the start of your next turn has disadvantage, and the first saving throw the creature makes before the start of your next turn has disadvantage. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Battle Cry (Intimidation).</b> You attempt to demoralize one humanoid you can see within 30 feet of you that can see and hear you. Make a Charisma (Intimidation) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Insight) check. If your check succeeds, the target is frightened until the end of your next turn. If the target was already frightened of you, it must immediately drop whatever it is holding. On its next turn, if it is still frightened of you, it must take the Dash action and move away from you by the safest available route on its turn, unless there is nowhere to move. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Charm (Persuasion).</b> You attempt to convince one humanoid you can see within 30 feet that can hear and understand you. Make a Charisma (Persuasion) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Insight) check. If you have dealt damage to the creature in the last hour, it has advantage on the check. If your check succeeds, the target is charmed by you until the start of your next turn, and it has disadvantage on the first attack roll it makes against a creature before the end of its next turn. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Confuse Beast (Animal Handling).</b> You attempt to confuse one beast on the battlefield. Make a Wisdom (Animal Handling) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Insight) check. If your check succeeds, the beast cannot take actions or reactions until the end of your next turn. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Distract (Performance).</b> You attempt to distract one beast or humanoid you can see within 30 feet of you that can see and hear you. Make a Charisma (Performance) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Insight) check. If your check succeeds, the next attack roll made against the target before the start of its next turn has advantage. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Emulate Predator (Nature).</b> You attempt to emulate the sounds of a natural predator of a beast or plant you can see within 30 feet. Make an Intelligence (Nature) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Insight) check. If your check succeeds, the target must take the Dash action and move away from you by the safest available route on its turn, unless there is nowhere to move. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Feint (Deception).</b> You attempt to divert the attention of a target you can see within 30 feet. Make a Charisma (Deception) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Insight) check. If your check succeeds, the first attack roll made against the target before the start of your next turn by someone other than you has advantage, and the target has disadvantage on the first saving throw they make against an effect caused by a creature other than you before the start of your next turn. If your check fails, the target can\'t be deceived by you in this way for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Hacktivate (Technology).</b> You attempt to determine the weaknesses in a droid you can see within 30 feet. Make an Intelligence (Technology) check contested by the target\'s Intelligence (Technology) check. If your check succeeds, you have advantage on the next attack roll you make against the target before the end of your turn, and if you hit, you deal additional damage equal to your Intelligence modifier. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Instruct (Investigation).</b> You attempt to find a weakness in your target. Make an Intelligence (Investigation) check contested by the target\'s Charisma (Deception) check. If your check succeeds, if a friendly creature makes an attack roll against the target and they can see and hear you, you can use your reaction to grant them advantage on the roll. If you do so, and they hit, they deal additional damage equal to your bonus to Investigation checks. This damage is the same type as the attack\'s damage. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Intuit (Insight).</b> You attempt to determine the motivations of one humanoid you can see within 30 feet. Make a Wisdom (Insight) check contested by the target\'s Charisma (Deception) check. If your check succeeds, the target can\'t have advantage on ability checks, attack rolls, or saving throws against you until the end of your next turn. If your check fails, the target instead can\'t have disadvantage on ability checks, attack rolls, or saving throws against you until the end of your next turn.\n"   " <b>Pocket Sand (Sleight of Hand).</b> You attempt to blind one beast or humanoid you can see within 15 feet of you. Make a Dexterity (Sleight of Hand) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Perception) check. If your check succeeds, the target is blinded until the end of your turn. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Precision Strike (Medicine).</b> You attempt to strike a pressure point in one humanoid within your reach. Make a Wisdom (Medicine) check contested by the target\'s Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check (the target chooses the ability to use). If your check succeeds, they are incapacitated until the end of their next turn. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Snare (Survival).</b> You attempt to cause a creature within 30 feet of you to stumble. Make a Wisdom (Survival) check contested by the target\'s Wisdom (Perception) check. If your check succeeds, and the target moves towards you before the start of your next turn, it gains 1 slowed level, and you can use your reaction to cause it to fall prone. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n"   " <b>Spin (Piloting).</b> You attempt to confound a piloted construct you can see within 30 feet. Make an Intelligence (Piloting) check contested by the target\'s Intelligence (Piloting) check. If your check succeeds, the target has disadvantage on attack rolls against you, and you have advantage on Dexterity saving throws against the target, until the start of your next turn. If your check fails, the target instead has advantage on attack rolls against you, and you have disadvantage on Dexterity saving throws against the target, until the start of your next turn.\n"   " <b>Study (Lore).</b> You attempt to anticipate your target\'s action. Make an Intelligence (Lore) check contested by the target\'s Charisma (Deception) check. If your check succeeds, you have advantage on the first ability check, attack roll or saving throw you make against that creature before the end of your next turn. Alternatively, before the end of your next turn, you can use your reaction to grant disadvantage on the first ability check, attack roll, or saving throw the target makes against you. If your check fails, you instead have disadvantage on the first ability check, attack roll or saving throw you make against that creature before the end of your next turn.\n"   " <b>Tumble (Acrobatics).</b> You attempt to make a quick tumble, immediately moving 10 feet. If you begin or end this movement within a creature\'s reach, make a Dexterity (Acrobatics) check contested by it\'s Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check (the target chooses the ability to use). If your check succeeds, this movement does not provoke opportunity attacks from it, and you have advantage on the first attack roll you make against it before the end of your turn. If your check fails, you immediately fall prone.\n"   " <b>Wrestle (Athletics).</b> You attempt to grab and pin a creature within 5 feet of you with at least one free hand. The target must be no more than one size larger than you. Make a Strength (Athletics) check contested by the target\'s Strength (Athletics) or Dexterity (Acrobatics) check (the target chooses the ability to use). If your check succeeds, the target is both grappled and restrained by you. If the target stops being grappled, it also stops being restrained. If your check fails, you can\'t use this feature on this target again for 1 hour.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nTechnologist\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou learn and can cast one 1st-level tech power once per long rest. Your techcasting ability is Intelligence. You require use of a wristpad for this power.\n"   " You can select this exploit multiple times. Each time you do so, you must choose a different power.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nWeaponmaster\'s Exploit</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain proficiency in three blasters or vibroweapons that lack the heavy and strength properties.\n"   " You can select this exploit multiple times. Each time you do so, you must choose different weapons.\n</font></string>
    <string name="acquisitions_practice"><font color="#D4af37">Acquisitions Practice</font></string>
    <string name="beguiler_practice"><font color="#D4af37">Beguiler Practice</font></string>
    <string name="beguiler_practice_forcecasting">Beguiler Practice ForCecasting</string>
    <string name="lethality_practice"><font color="#D4af37">Lethality Practice</font></string>
    <string name="sharpshooter_practice"><font color="#D4af37">Sharpshooter Practice</font></string>
    <string name="sneak_attack">Sneak\nAttack</string>

    <!--Scholar-->
    <string name="scholar">ScHoLAX</string>
    <string name="the_scholar">the ScHoLAX</string>
    <string name="gambler_pursuit"><font color="#D4af37">Gambler Pursuit</font></string>
    <string name="gambler_discoveries">Gambler Discoveries</string>
    <string name="physician_pursuit"><font color="#D4af37">Physician Pursuit</font></string>
    <string name="physician_discoveries">Physician Discoveries</string>
    <string name="politician_pursuit"><font color="#D4af37">Politician Pursuit</font></string>
    <string name="politician_discoveries">Politician Discoveries</string>
    <string name="tactician_pursuit"><font color="#D4af37">Tactician Pursuit</font></string>
    <string name="tactician_discoveries">Tactician Discoveries</string>
    <string name="discoveries"><font color="#D4af37">Discoveries</font></string>
    <string name="discoveriesHeader">Discoveries</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table">Side Effects</string>
    <string name="d20_side_effects">d20 Side Effects</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table1">The creature turns out to be allergic to this specific\ntreatment. Every ability score is reduced by 1</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table2">The creature starts sneezing uncontrollably. Any attack\nrolls with a die roll value of 19 results in a miss due to a\npoorly timed sneeze.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table3">The creature\'s legs become swollen. The creature gains\n1 slowed level.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table4">The creature becomes one size larger or smaller.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table5">The skin at their joints turns into a wooden material,\ngiving them a bonus of +2 to AC.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table6">The creature\'s body starts producing powerful stomach\nacid in high amounts. The creature can use an action to\nspew stomach acid in a 15 feet cone. The DC for this\nsaving throw equals 8 + your proficiency bonus + your\nConstitution modifier. A creature takes 2d6 acid damage\non a failed save, and half as much damage on a\nsuccessful one. The damage increases to 3d6 at 5th\nlevel, 4d6 at 11th level, and 5d6 at 17th level.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table7">The creature becomes mute and has uncontrollable gas.\nThey have disadvantage on Dexterity (Stealth) checks\nthat rely on smell.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table8">The creature\'s eyes glows bright red. The creature also\ngains darkvision, but if they already have darkvision\nthey get a light headache instead.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table9">The creature gains advantage on perception checks\nbased on hearing, but everything seems uncomfortably\nloud to them. They gain vulnerability to sonic damage.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table10">The treatment slows down their brain function\nreducing their Intelligence by 4.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table11">The creature\'s skin turns dark purple. If they are already\npurple, they turn bright pink instead.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table12">The creature becomes covered in sickly, green pustules.\nWhen the creature is hit by a melee attack, the attacker\ntakes 1d4 poison damage.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table13">The creature\'s skin starts to seriously bloat up from\ninternal pressure build-up, and a strong impact may\ncause it to explode. Whenever the creature takes\ndamage, the creature has to pass a concentration check\nor the creature takes kinetic damage equal to half their\nmaximum hit points. Other creatures within 10 feet of\nthe explosion also take a fourth of the damage. Once\nthis explosion occurs, their skin becomes very soft.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table14">The creature rapidly grows body hair all over, including\nthe face, until they resemble a wookiee. If they are\nalready a wookiee, the reverse effect occurs; all hair\nimmediately falls off, leaving the skin bare.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table15">The creature\'s body temperature fluctuates to\nextremes. They gain resistance to cold and fire damage.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table16">The creature becomes ravenous. Every hour they\nhaven\'t eaten a meal they gain a level of exhaustion.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table17">The creature believes they are the chosen one.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table18">The creature has a difficult time resting. The amount\nthey heal from Hit Dice is now halved.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table19">The creature\'s movement speed is increased by 15 feet,\nand opportunity attacks on them have disadvantage.</string>
    <string name="side_effects_table20">The creature gains 10d10 hit points, and they feel happy\nand carefree.</string>

    <!--Scout-->
    <string name="scout">ScouT</string>
    <string name="the_scout">the ScouT</string>
    <string name="scout_routines"><font color="#D4af37">Scout Routines</font></string>
    <string name="routines_known">Routines\nKnown</string>
    <string name="routine_radius">Routine\nRadius</string>
    <string name="scout_routinesHeader">Scout Routines</string>
    <string name="scout_routinestext"><font face="sans-serif">The routines are presented in alphabetical order. If multiple scouts grant the same routine, affected creatures can only benefit from it once. You must be conscious to grant the benefit of your routines.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nAdaptability Routine</font><font face="sans-serif">\nAt the start of each of your turns, you can choose an ability score with a saving throw in which you are not proficient. Until the start of your next turn, you add half your proficiency bonus to saving throws you make with the chosen ability. Alternatively, you can choose to extend this benefit to allies within 5 feet of you.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nMaven\'s Routine</font><font face="sans-serif">\nAt the start of each of your turns, you can choose to gain resistance to damage from tech powers until the start of your next turn. Alternatively, you can choose to extend this benefit to allies within 5 feet of you.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nMesmer\'s Routine</font><font face="sans-serif">\nAt the start of each of your turns, you can choose to have advantage on saving throws against effects that would incapacitate you or put you to sleep until the start of your next turn. Alternatively, you can choose to extend this benefit to allies within 5 feet of you.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nNomad\'s Routine</font><font face="sans-serif">\nAt the start of each of your turns, you can choose to gain advantage on Constitution saving throws to avoid exhaustion from unenhanced sources, as well as being naturally adapted to both hot and cold climates. Alternatively, you can choose to extend this benefit to allies within 5 feet of you.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nXesponder\'s Routine</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you roll initiative, you can choose to add your proficiency bonus to the initiative check and have advantage on attack rolls against creatures that have not yet acted. Alternatively, you can choose to allow each friendly creature within 5 feet of you to add half your proficiency bonus to the initiative check and have advantage on the first attack roll they make against a creature that has not yet acted.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nSharpshooter\'s Routine</font><font face="sans-serif">\nAt the start of each of your turns, you can choose to gain a bonus to the first weapon attack roll you make before the start of your next turn equal to your Intelligence modifier. Alternatively, you can choose to allow each friendly creature within 5 feet of you to add half your Intelligence modifier to the first weapon attack roll they make before the start of your next turn.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nStrider\'s Routine</font><font face="sans-serif">\nAt the start of each of your turns, you can choose to have each slowed level only reduce your speed by 5 feet, unless it would reduce your speed to 0 until the start of your next turn. Alternatively, you can choose to extend this benefit to allies within 5 feet of you.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nWarden\'s Routine</font><font face="sans-serif">\nAt the start of each of your turns, you can choose to gain a crawling, climbing, and swimming speed equal to your walking speed until the start of your next turn. Alternatively, you can choose to extend this benefit to allies within 5 feet of you.\n</font></string>
    <string name="bulwark_technique"><font color="#D4af37">Bulwark Technique</font></string>
    <string name="hunter_technique"><font color="#D4af37">Hunter Technique</font></string>
    <string name="slayer_technique"><font color="#D4af37">Slayer Technique</font></string>
    <string name="stalker_technique"><font color="#D4af37">Stalker Technique</font></string>
    <string name="ranger_quarry">Ranger\'s\nQuarry</string>

    <!--Sentinel-->
    <string name="sentinel">SENTiNEL</string>
    <string name="the_sentinel">The SENTiNEL</string>
    <string name="sentinel_ideals"><font color="#D4af37">Sentinel Ideals</font></string>
    <string name="ideals_known">Ideals\nKnown</string>
    <string name="ideal_manifests">Ideal\nManifests</string>
    <string name="sentinel_idealsHeader">Sentinel ideals</string>
    <string name="sentinel_idealstext"><font face="sans-serif">the ideals are presented in alphabetical order.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the Agile</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain a swimming speed and a climbing speed equal to your walking speed. When you make a long jump, you can cover a number of feet up to twice your Wisdom or Charisma score (your choice). When you make a high jump, you can leap a number of feet up into the air equal to 3 + twice your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice).\n"    "Additionally, as a bonus action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. For the next minute, opportunity attacks against you are made with disadvantage.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the Artisan</font><font face="sans-serif">\nChoose one of your skill or tool proficiencies. When you make an ability check with the chosen skill or tool, you can add half your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice, minimum of one).\n"    "Additionally, as an action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. For the next 10 minutes, the bonus increases to your Wisdom or Charisma modifier, and you can choose a second skill or tool to extend this feature to.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the contender</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYour unarmed strike damage increases by one step (from 1 to d4, d4 to d6, or d6 to d8), and your unarmed strikes gain the finesse property.\n"    "Additionally, as a bonus action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. For the next minute, your unarmed strikes count as enhanced for the purpose of overcoming resistance and immunity to unenhanced attacks and damage, and you can use your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice) instead of Strength for checks made to grapple a target or escape a grapple.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the Fighter</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the fighting style options, detailed in Chapter 6.\n"    "Additionally, as a bonus action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. For the next minute, you know the fighting mastery that corresponds with the fighting style you chose with this feature. If you already know that fighting mastery, you instead learn another of your choice for the duration.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the Hunter</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain darkvision out to a range of 60 feet. If you already have darkvision, this ideal increases its range by 30 feet.\n"    "Additionally, as a bonus action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. For the next minute, you can see normally in enhanced darkness, and you gain blindsight to 10 feet.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the Steadfast</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you would make a melee weapon attack roll, you can instead force the target to make a Dexterity saving throw (DC = 8 + your bonus to attacks with the weapon). If you would have advantage on your attack roll, the creature instead has disadvantage on their saving throw, and if you would have disadvantage on your attack roll, the creature instead has advantage on their saving throw. On a failed save, the target takes normal weapon damage and is subjected to any additional effects that would occur on a hit.\n"    "Additionally, as a bonus action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. For the next minute, when a creature succeeds on the saving throw, they take half the normal weapon damage, and when a creature rolls a 1 on the saving throw, they treat the damage as if you had rolled the maximum.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the Titan</font><font face="sans-serif">\nYou gain proficiency in medium armor.\n"    "Additionally, as a bonus action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. For the next minute, you have advantage on ability checks and attack rolls that would forcefully move another creature, and the distance they would be moved increases by 5 feet.\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the Tranquil</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you finish a short or long rest, you gain a number of temporary force points equal to half your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice, minimum of one). When you would spend a force point while you have temporary force points, the temporary force points are spent first. All temporary force points are lost at the end of your next short or long rest.\n"    "Additionally, as an action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. You regain a number of force points equal to half your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice, minimum of one).\n</font>
            <font size="24">\nideal of the vigorous</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen you roll a Hit Die to regain hit points, you may use your Wisdom or Charisma modifier in place of your Constitution modifier when determining the number of hit points you regain.\n"    "Additionally, as an action, you can manifest this ideal in a brief surge of energy. You gain a number of temporary hit points equal to half your sentinel level + your Wisdom or Charisma modifier (your choice,minimum of one).\n</font></string>
    <string name="path_of_the_corsair"><font color="#D4af37">Path of the Corsair</font></string>
    <string name="path_of_focus"><font color="#D4af37">Path of Focus</font></string>
    <string name="path_of_the_forceblade"><font color="#D4af37">Path of the Forceblade</font></string>
    <string name="path_of_shadows"><font color="#D4af37">Path of Shadows</font></string>
    <string name="kinetic_combat">Kinetic\nCombat</string>


    <!--Class info-->
    <string name="classinfotext"><font size="26">A</font><font face="sans-serif">dventurers are extraordinary people, driven by a thirst for excitement into a life that others would never dare lead. They are heroes, compelled to explore the dark places of the world and take on the challenges that lesser women and men can\'t stand against.\n"   " Class is the primary definition of what your character can do. It\'s more than a profession; it\'s your character\'s calling. Class shapes the way you think about the world and interact with it and your relationship with other people and powers in the galaxy. A fighter, for example, might view the world in pragmatic terms of strategy and maneuvering, and see herself as just a pawn in a much larger game. A consular, by contrast, might see himself as a willing servant of the Force. While the fighter has contacts in a mercenary company or army, the consular might know a number of Jedi or Sith who share his faith.\n"   " Your class gives you a variety of special features, such as a fighter\'s mastery of weapons and armor, and an engineer\'s powers. At low levels, your class gives you only two or three features, but as you advance in level you gain more and your existing features often improve. Each class entry in this chapter includes a table summarizing the benefits you gain at every level, as well as a detailed explanation of each one. At 3rd level, each class gains an archetype, or subclass, that helps that class focus in a specific direction or enable an entirely new playstyle, such as allowing raging in heavy armor for Juggernaut Approach berserkers or granting techcasting to Shield Specialist fighters. Each archetype grants additional features at higher levels, varying by class, as shown in the class table.\n"   " Additionally, each class has a second level of customization, such as a consular\'s Force-Empowered Casting or a scholar\'s Discoveries. The level at which each class obtains this second level varies. If a class\'s customization requires a level, that refers to class level. If a customization has prerequisites, the character must meet them to learn it. A character can learn a customization at the same time it meets the customization\'s prerequisites. Unless otherwise specified, a customization can only be taken once.\n\n</font></string>
    <string name="primary_ability">Primary\nAbility</string>
    <string name="saving_throw_proficiencies">Saving Throw\nProficiencies</string>
    <string name="hit_die">Hit\nDie</string>
    <string name="multiclassingbox"><font size="22"><b>Multiclassing</b></font><font face="sans-serif">\nAdventurers sometimes advance in more than one class. An operative might switch direction in life and become an engineer, or a berserker might discover latent Force-sensitivity and dabble in the guardian class while continuing to advance as a berserker. Optional rules for combining classes in this way, called multiclassing, appear below.</font></string>
    <string name="multiclassingText"><font size="26">Multiclassing</font><font face="sans-serif">\n\nMulticlassing allows you to gain levels in multiple classes. Doing so lets you mix the abilities of those classes to realize a character concept that might not be reflected in one of the standard class options.\n"   " With this rule, you have the option of gaining a level in a new class whenever you advance in level, instead of gaining a level in your current class. Your levels in all your classes are added together to determine your character level. For example, if you have three levels in consular and two in fighter, you\'re a 5th-level character.\n"   " As you advance in levels, you might primarily remain a member of your original class with just a few levels in another class, or you might change course entirely, never looking back at the class you left behind. You might even start progressing in a third or fourth class. Compared to a single-class character of the same level, you\'ll sacrifice some focus in exchange for versatility.\n\n</font></string>
    <string name="multiclassing_classfeatures"><font size="26">class Features</font><font face="sans-serif">\n\nWhen you gain a new level in a class, you get its features for that level. Some features, however, have additional rules when you\'re multiclassing, as shown below.\n</font></string>
    <string name="multiclassing_example"><font size="22"><b>Multiclassing Example</b></font><font face="sans-serif">\nDrew is playing a 4th-level fighter. When his character earns enough experience points to reach 5th level, Drew decides that his character will multiclass instead of continuing to progress as a fighter. Drew\'s fighter has been spending a lot of time with Rickey\'s scout, and has even been doing some jobs on the side for the Bounty Broker\'s Association as a bounty hunter. Drew decides that his character will multiclass into the operative class, and thus his character becomes a 4thlevel fighter and 1st-level operative (written as fighter 4/operative 1).\n"   " When Drew\'s character earns enough experience to reach 6th level, he can decide whether to add another fighter level (becoming a fighter 5/operative 1), another operative level (becoming a fighter 4/operative 2), or a level in a third class, perhaps dabbling in the Force thanks to a Sith holocron he acquired (becoming a fighter 4/operative 1/consular 1).</font></string>
    <string name="multiclassing_highlvlcasting"><font size="22">High Level casting</font><font face="sans-serif">\nWhen determining the number of higher level powers you can cast before needing a long rest, consult the rules for casting in the class in which you have the most levels.\n</font></string>

    <!--Species-->
    <string name="species_info1"><font size="26"><b>A</b></font><font face="sans-serif">"  "visit to any of the great cities in the worlds of Star Wars overwhelms the senses. Voices chatter in countless different languages. The smells of cooking in dozens of different cuisines mingle with the odors of crowded streets and poor sanitation. Buildings in myriad architectural styles display the diverse origins of their inhabitants.\n"   " And the people themselves-people of varying size, shape, and color, dressed in a dazzling spectrum of styles and hues-represent many different species, from diminutive bothans and stalwart cereans to majestic twi\'leks and towering wookiees, mingling among a variety of human ethnicities.\n"   " Scattered among the members of these more common species are the true exotics: a hulking besalisk here, pushing his way through the crowd, and a sly chiss there, lurking in the shadows with mischief in her eyes. A group of jawas chatters as one of them activates a clever mechanical toy that moves of its own accord. Zabraks and devaronians live and work alongside humans, without fully belonging. And there, well out of the sunlight, is a lone dros-a fugitive from the Galactic Republic, trying to make his way in a world.\n</font></string>
    <string name="species_info2Header">choosing a species</string>
    <string name="species_info2Text">Humans are the most common people in the worlds of Star Wars, but they live and work alongside ithorians, kiffar, mirialan, and countless other fantastic species. Your character belongs to one of these peoples.\n"   " Your choice of species affects many different aspects of your character. It establishes fundamental qualities that exist throughout your character\'s adventuring career. When making this decision, keep in mind the kind of character you want to play. For example, a bothan can be a good choice for a sneaky operative, a wookiee makes a tough berserker, and a twi\'lek can be a master of the Force.\n"   " Your character species not only affects your ability scores and traits but also provides the cues for building your character\'s story. Each species\' description in this chapter includes information to help you roleplay a character of that species, including personality, physical appearance, features of society, and special alignment tendencies. These details are suggestions to help you think about your character; adventurers can deviate widely from the norm for their species. It\'s worthwhile to consider why your character is different, as a helpful way to think about your character\'s background and personality.\n</string>
    <string name="species_info3Header">Special Traits</string>
    <string name="species_info3Text"><font face="sans-serif">The description of each species includes special traits that are common to members of that species. The following entries appear among the traits of most species.\n</font>
        <font size="22">\nAbility Score increase</font> <font face="sans-serif">\nEvery species increases one or more of a character\'s ability scores.\n</font>
        <font size="22">\nAge</font> <font face="sans-serif">\nThe age entry notes the age when a member of the species is considered an adult, as well as the species\' expected lifespan. This information can help you decide how old your character is at the start of the game. You can choose any age for your character, which could provide an explanation for some of your ability scores. For example, if you play a young or very old character, your age could explain a particularly low Strength or Constitution score, while advanced age could account for a high Intelligence or Wisdom.\n</font>
        <font size="22">\nAlignment</font> <font face="sans-serif">\nMost species have tendencies toward certain alignments, described in this entry. These are not binding for player characters, but considering why your sith pureblood follows the light side, for example, in defiance of the Sith Empire can help you better define your character.\n</font>
        <font size="22">\nSize</font> <font face="sans-serif">\nCharacters of most species are Medium, a size category including creatures that are roughly 4 to 8 feet tall. Members of a few species are Small (between 2 and 4 feet tall), which means that certain rules of the game affect them differently. The most important of these rules is that Small characters have trouble wielding heavy weapons and heavy shields, as explained in chapter 6.\n</font>
        <font size="22">\nSpeed</font> <font face="sans-serif">\nYour speed determines how far you can move when traveling (chapter 8) and fighting (chapter 9).\n</font>
        <font size="22">\nLanguages</font> <font face="sans-serif">\nBy virtue of your species, your character can speak, read, and write certain languages. Each species typically speaks, or at least understands, Galactic Basic as well as having a unique language of their own. Chapter 4 lists the most common languages of the Star Wars universe.</font></string>
    <!--Bith-->
    <string name="bith">BiTH</string>
    <string name="bith_example">Bith Example</string>
    <string name="bith_info1">Bith are craniopods with pale pink, yellow, or green skin, large heads, large lidless eyes, toe less feet, and long fingers. Their thumb and small finger were both fully opposable. The bith\'s internal systems are different from most humanoids, as the bith have only one lung, and exhale through their skin. Bith also lack a proper nose, instead having highly sensitive olfactory organs hidden in the skin-flaps of their cheeks.\n"   " The other bith senses are also acute. Bith can sense the tonal qualities of sound as well as other species sensed colors. Their eyes, as big as a Menahuun\'s, can see microscopic details of nearby objects, but are extremely nearsighted as a result. An interesting side effect of their incredible sensors is the effect of sonic grenades, or screamers, on them. It is described as causing their heads to explode. Similarly, bith have high manual dexterity which helps them manipulate fine tools, though their physical prowess with gross motor skills was only average.</string>
    <string name="bith_info2">Bith are one of the galaxy\'s most ancient civilizations, with a history going back millions of years. This antiquity garners respect in certain quarters, such as among the Gree, who gave them more respect than other, "younger" species. Their society is highly regimented, with everything from mate selection to political leadership controlled by sophisticated computer programs.</string>
    <string name="bith_info3">Bith names are quite diverse. Some names look complicated and difficult to pronounce, while others are quite simple.</string>
    <string name="bith_traitsHeader">Bith Traits</string>
    <string name="bith_traitsText">As a bith, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Intelligence score increases by 2, and your Dexterity score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Bith reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Biths\' benevolent nature causes them to tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Bith typically stand 5 to 6 feet tall and generally weigh about 120 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Detail Oriented</b>. You are practiced at scouring for details. You have advantage on Intelligence (Investigation) checks within 5 feet.\n"   " <b>Keen Hearing and Smell</b>. You have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks that involve hearing or smell.\n"   " <b>Musician</b>. You are proficient in one musical instrument of your choice. <b>Programmer</b>. Whenever you make an Intelligence (Technology) check related to computers, you are considered to have expertise in the Technology skill.\n"   " <b>Sonic Sensitivity</b>. Your powerful sense of hearing makes you especially vulnerable to deafening sounds. You have disadvantage on saving throws against effects that would deal sonic damage (explained in chapter 9).\n"   " <b>Trance</b>. You only need 3 hours of sleep during a long rest to gain its benefits, instead of 6. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it to gain its benefits.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic, Bith, and one more language of your choice.</string>
    <!--Bothan-->
    <string name="bothan">BoTHAN</string>
    <string name="bothan_example">Bothan Example</string>
    <string name="bothan_info1">Bothans are a short species of furry humanoids. Bothans are covered in fur which shifted in response to their emotional state by way of gentle ripplings. It is this trait, named Wrendui, that betrays them when members of their kind intend to be duplicitous in their dealings with others. They possess tapered pointed ears, and both males and females were known to sport beards.\n"   " Bothans are able to interbreed with the other species, though it is rare that they do so. Such hybrids somewhat resembled baseline humans with haunches, hooves, fur, pointed ears and a long tail.</string>
    <string name="bothan_info2">Bothan culture is guided by the philosophy and principles from the ancient text known as The Way, written by Golm Fervse\'dra. In this "Bothan Way", the pursuit of power and influence is paramount. Thus, individual bothans put their own political and economic success above all other concerns, and as a species, bothans put their own advancement ahead of other intergalactic interests. The volume of backstabbing, subtle character assassination and political maneuvering in bothan society is dizzying, and results in many species stereotyping bothans as untrustworthy. In fact, most bothans are habitually paranoid, believing that anyone who\'s not working with them, is working against them. In times of crisis, the focus of bothan society shifts to a survivalist state known as "ar\'krai". When engaged in ar\'krai, all fit bothans volunteer to defend their species from impending extinction.</string>
    <string name="bothan_info3">Male bothan names are often trickey while female\'s are soft. Surnames are familial.</string>
    <string name="bothan_traitsHeader">Bothan Traits</string>
    <string name="bothan_traitsText">As a bothan, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Intelligence score increases by 2, and your Dexterity score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Bothans reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Bothans\' duplicitous nature causes them to tend toward the dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Bothans stand 4–5 feet tall and weigh under 100 pounds. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Naturally Stealthy</b>. You can attempt to hide even when you are obscured only by a creature that is your size or larger than you.\n"   " <b>Nimble Escape</b>. You can take the Disengage or Hide action as a bonus action on each of your turns.</string>
    <string name="bothan_traitsTextBox">While bothans are suitable for many classes, they most iconically fit as operatives. The Nimble Escape special trait heavily overlaps with the operative\'s <b>Cunning Action</b> feature, however, making this species/class combination counterintuitive. If, during the character creation part of your game, a player decides to make a bothan operative, consider letting them use the following feature instead:\n"   " <b>Versatile Expertise</b>. You gain proficiency in one skill of your choice. You gain expertise in one skill of your choice in which you are proficient.</string>
    <string name="bothan_traitsText2">"   " <b>Shrewd</b>. You are proficient in the Insight and Deception skills.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Bothese. Bothese had a great influence on the forming of Galactic Basic; the two languages share many cognates.</string>
    <!--Cathar-->
    <string name="cathar">cATHAX</string>
    <string name="cathar_example">Cathar Example</string>
    <string name="cathar_info1">The Cathar have fur-covered bodies with thick manes as well as prominent, retractable claws that can deliver powerful killing attacks on foes and prey. Their bodies also possess rapid healing abilities. These traits make them the perfect hand-to-hand specialists.\n"   " The Cathar species also has two subspecies, known as the Juhani and the Myr Rho. Both of these are notably less catlike than mainline Cathar. Cathar are born into a litter. The Cathar species is biologically similar to the Bothan species.</string>
    <string name="cathar_info2">On their homeworld, Cathar live in cities built into giant trees, and are organized into clans governed by elders. Stories of their great heroes were often carved into the trunks of these tree-homes for following generations to see. The Cathar mate for life, to the extent that when one mate dies, the survivor never has a relationship with another. Cathar clan society includes great pageants and celebrations, especially for their heroes. Their religion includes a ritual known as the "Blood Hunt," in which Cathar warriors individually engaged in combat against entire nests of Kiltik in order to gain honor and purge themselves of inner darkness. The native language of the Cathar is Catharese, which included the emphasis of some spoken words with a growl.</string>
    <string name="cathar_info3">Cathar names can sound both melodic and fairly gutteral, but they almost always sound strong and fierce. Female names are typically longer than male names. Surnames are usually one syllable.</string>
    <string name="cathar_traitsHeader">cathar Traits</string>
    <string name="cathar_traitsText">As a cathar, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, and your Charisma score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Cathar reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Cathar tend toward no particular\n"   " <b>alignment</b>. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Cathar range from 5 to 7 feet tall, and can weigh up to 300 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Cat\'s Claws</b>. Your unarmed strikes deal 1d6 kinetic damage and have the finesse property.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Your vision can easily cut through darkness. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Leonine Agility</b>. Your reflexes and agility allow you to move with a burst of speed. When you move on your turn in combat, you can double your speed until the end of the turn. Once you use this trait, you can’t use it again until you move 0 feet on one of your turns.\n"   " <b>Silent Step</b>. You have proficiency in the Stealth skill.\n"   " <b>Treeclimber</b>. You have a climbing speed of 30 feet. You have advantage on Strength saving throws and Strength (Athletics) checks that involve climbing.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Catharese.</string>
    <!--Cerean-->
    <string name="cerean">cEXEAN</string>
    <string name="cerean_example">Cerean Example</string>
    <string name="cerean_info1">The Cereans\' enlarged skulls, extending above their foreheads, house complex binary brains, provided with sufficient blood by an extra heart in their heads. The binary structure of Cerean thinking helps them to ponder two sides of an issue at once. It also enables them to process information and solve problems rapidly and provides a highly advanced capacity for concentration and meditation. Because of their thoughtful nature, they tend to be calm, rational and analytical, preferring peaceful philosophies and a lifestyle which works in harmony with nature. Though the quick-thinking Cereans have equally quick reflexes, they are commonly not as well coordinated as humans.</string>
    <string name="cerean_info2">Cereans developed a low-tech society on their homeworld and prefer to live in isolation from the wider galaxy. Preserving the natural beauty of Cerea, the planet is home to many Outsider Citadels where it is permissible to use offworld technology, though it could not be removed from the Citadel. Meditation is a core part of a Cerean\'s daily rituals, with many employing specially-forged kasha crystals as a focusing tool. By focusing one\'s thoughts while in contact with such crystals, distractions are eliminated, creating an exceptional meditation environment. Cerean Jedi sometimes incorporate these crystals into their lightsabers, providing great focus, even during intense physical combat.</string>
    <string name="cerean_info3">Cerean male first names are often hyphenated, while females are not. Surnames are familial.</string>
    <string name="cerean_traitsHeader">cerean Traits</string>
    <string name="cerean_traitsText">As a cerean, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Intelligence score increases by 2, and your Wisdom score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Cereans reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Cereans\' altruistic nature causes them to tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Cereans typically stand between 6 and 7 feet tall and weigh about 150 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Intuitive Initiative</b>. You can choose to reroll Initiative checks, but you must use the new roll.\n"   " <b>Natural Instinct</b>. You have proficiency with Nature or Perception (your choice).\n"   " <b>Prediction</b>. You can embrace the Force and use your advanced insight to predict likely outcomes, allowing you to turn failures into successes. When you roll a 1 on an attack roll, ability check, or saving throw, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll.\n"   " <b>Second Heart</b>. When you are reduced to 0 hit points but not killed outright, you can drop to 1 hit point instead. You can’t use this feature again until you finish a long rest.\n"   " <b>Trance</b>. You only need 3 hours of sleep during a long rest to gain its benefits, instead of 6. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it to gain its benefits.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Cerean. Cerean is characterized by its gravelly sounds.</string>
    <!--Chiss-->
    <string name="chiss">cHiSS</string>
    <string name="chiss_example">Chiss Example</string>
    <string name="chiss_info1">The chiss are a near-human species distinguished by their blue skin and glowing red eyes. Genetic analysis indicate that they are an offshoot of humanity, and it is believed that moving underground led to a divergence between them and baseline Humans. Their blue skin, jet black hair and red eyes generally command attention; these features make them physically striking and instantly recognizable.</string>
    <string name="chiss_info2">Chiss society is highly structured and ordered with the rule of law being enforced by a group of four affiliations known as the Ruling Families: the Csapla, Nuruodo, Inrokini and Sabosen. These are not biological family groupings but instead different branches of their government. Every chiss claims affiliation to one of the four families, as determined by both tradition and place of birth. The family names are more of a cultural holdover; the bloodlines had grown so co-meddled that any chiss could claim affiliation to any of the ruling families. In spite of the outward impression of calm and order that the chiss like to project to outsiders, there were evidently tensions within the Families; political assassinations are a real part of chiss political life for the Ruling Families.</string>
    <string name="chiss_info3">A chiss true-name has 3 parts, each separated by an apostrophe. The first part is their family name, the second part is their root name, and the third part is their occupation. Chiss rarely share their true-name with non-chiss, and usually go by their root name. Male and female names do not significantly deviate.\n"   "<b>Names:</b> Crorcu\'ecuk\'unist, Dash\'esoru\'ishur, Jerd\'ecer\'lonii, Kisk\'egauw\'eqhi, Marag\'aliphil\'eduo, Pommo\'icuote\'nlerme, Vornu\'wuzi\'lerdim</string>
    <string name="chiss_traitsHeader">chiss Traits</string>
    <string name="chiss_traitsText">As a chiss, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Intelligence score increases by 2, and your Charisma score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Chiss reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Chiss\' tactical and selfish nature cause them to tend toward lawful dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Chiss typically stand between 5 and 6 feet tall and weigh about 160 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Martial Proficiency</b>. You have proficiency with light and medium armor as well as the heavy pistol and sniper rifle.\n"   " <b>Politically Minded</b>. You have proficiency in the Insight skill.\n"   " <b>Tech Resistance</b>. Growing up around technology leaves an impact on chiss. You have advantage on Dexterity and Intelligence saving throws against tech powers.\n"   " <b>Superior Darkvision</b>. Your vision can easily cut through darkness. You can see in dim light within 120 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic, Cheunh, and your choice of Minnisiat or Sy Bisti. Cheunh is a complex language that is difficult for nonchiss to learn. Chiss take pride in this difficulty. Communications with outsiders are conducted through local trade-languages like Minnisiat or Sy Bisti.</string>
    <!--Devaronian-->
    <string name="devaronian">DEvAXoNiAN</string>
    <string name="devaronian_example">Devaronian Example</string>
    <string name="devaronian_info1">A bipedal mammalian species, Devaronians evolved in the dense jungles of Devaron as a hunter-gather species. Their bodies are denser than most humanoids\' and as a result they were heavier than their appearance would tend to indicate. Devaronians have silver-based blood, which appears thick and black when exposed. They possess a unique blood filtration and cleansing system which processes through two livers. Because their bodies are constantly cleansed of toxins and carcinogens, the species is highly resistant to poison. To this end, sulfur is used as a stimulant on Devaron to enhance speed and strength, because inhaling it causes the substance to enter the bloodstream rapidly. Their livers struggle to eliminate sulfur from their system, meaning that long-term use can be dangerous.</string>
    <string name="devaronian_info2">Devaronian males are driven by an urge to wander, usually taking the first opportunity to move on from one place to another; they are often found traveling the galaxy as tramp freighter captains and scouts. Female Devaronians, on the other hand, are content to remain in a single location, raising the young and running the government of Devaron. The males send money back to their homeworld to support their families, but otherwise hardly ever return. The females are content with this arrangement, as they tend to view the restless males as disruptive to home life.</string>
    <string name="devaronian_info3">Devaronian names are dark, complex and often guttural, with some harsher tones mixed in here and there.</string>
    <string name="devaronian_traitsHeader">Devaronian Traits</string>
    <string name="devaronian_traitsText">As a devaronian, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Constitution score increases by 2, and your Charisma score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Devaronians reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Devaronians\' greediness causes them to tend toward chaotic balanced, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Devaronians typically stand between 5 and 6 feet tall and weigh about 160 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Curiosity</b>. You have proficiency with Survival or Investigation (your choice).\n"   " <b>Heat Adaptation</b>. You have advantage on Constitution saving throws made to avoid exhaustion due to extreme heat.\n"   " <b>Jungle Dweller</b>. Growing up in the jungles of Devaron has left an impact. You don’t treat jungle terrain as difficult terrain.\n"   " <b>Silver Tongue</b>. You have proficiency with Deception or Persuasion (your choice).\n"   " <b>Tech Resistance</b>. Growing up around technology leaves an impact on devaronians. You have advantage on Dexterity and Intelligence saving throws against tech powers.\n"   " <b>Two Livered</b>. Devaronians have two livers, which makes them adept at filtering toxins. You have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you have resistance against poison damage (explained in chapter 9).\n<b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Devaronese. Devaronese is characterized by grunts and grumbles. It is rare to hear a Devaronian speak it anywhere other than their homeworld of Devaron.</string>
    <!--Droid class 1-->
    <string name="droid_class_1">DXoiD cLASS 1</string>
    <string name="droid_class_1_example">Droid class 1 Example</string>
    <string name="droid_class_1_info1">Class I droids are typically vaguely human-like in both shape and size, standing at around 6 feet, although some are smaller. They are usually a polished metallic color, though this can vary based on tasks for which they are created, their affiliation, or quirks of their owner.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_1_info2">Class I droids are programmed for the mathematical, medical, or physical sciences. Subcategories of the first degree are medical droids, biological science droids, physical science droids, and mathematics droids.\n"   " Medical droids, also known as meddroids, med droids, medical units or surgical droids are a type of droid designed to heal living beings, and are the most commonly found Class I droids.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_1_info3">Droids are typically called by their designation, given to them when they are created, or some affectation given to them by their owner. Often this affectation is a play on their designation. Occasionally, noteworthy droids will earn monikers based on their accomplishments.\n"   " <b>Designations (Names)</b>. 2MED2 (Toomedtoo), GH-7 (Geeaych-Seven), TX-20 (Tee-Ex Twenty)</string>
    <string name="droid_class_1_traitsHeader">class 1 Droid Traits</string>
    <string name="droid_class_1_traitsText">As a class I droid, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Intelligence score increases by 2, and your Wisdom or Charisma score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Droids don\'t age, though they require maintenance to retain functionality.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Droids tend toward no particular alignment. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Class I droids stand between 5 and 6 feet tall and weigh about 170 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 25 feet. Type. Your creature type is droid.\n"   " <b>Armor Integration</b>. You can not wear armor, but you can have the armor professionally integrated into your chassis over the course of a long rest. This work must be done by someone proficient with astrotech\'s <b>implements</b>. You must be proficient in armor in order to have it integrated. <b>Droid Resistances</b>. You are resistant to necrotic, poison, and psychic damage, and are immune to poison and disease. <b>Droid Systems</b>. You do not need to eat, drink, or breathe. Additionally, you no longer require a tech focus to cast tech powers. <b>Droid Vulnerabilities</b>. You are vulnerable to ion damage. Additionally, you have disadvantage on saving throws against effects that would deal ion or lightning damage. <b>Force-Insensitive</b>. While droids can be manipulated by many force powers, they can not sense the Force. You can not use force powers or take levels in forcecasting classes. <b>Knowledge Protocol</b>. You have proficiency in two Intelligence, Wisdom, or Charisma skills of your choice. <b>Maintenance Mode</b>. Rather than sleep, you must spend 3 hours performing routine maintenance during a long rest to gain its benefits, during which you have disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it. <b>Rapid Reconstruction</b>. You are built with internal repair mechanisms. As a bonus action, you can choose to spend one of your Hit Dice to recover hit points. <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and one language of your choice. You can understand spoken and written Binary, but you can not speak it.</string>
    <!--Droid class 2-->
    <string name="droid_class_2">DXoiD cLASS 2</string>
    <string name="droid_class_2_example">Droid class 2 Example</string>
    <string name="droid_class_2_info1">Class II droids are typically small, standing between two and four feet. Their form and color scheme vary based on tasks for which they are created, their affiliation, or quirks of their owner.\n"   " They are noteworthy for their distinct, functionoriented form.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_2_info2">Class II droids are programmed for engineering and other technical sciences. They differ from class one droids because they apply the science to real-life situations. Class II droids are rarely equipped with Basic vocabulators, instead communicating through Binary. There are five subcategories of class II droids. Astromech, exploration, environmental, engineering, and maintenance droids are all class II droids.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_2_info3">Droids are typically called by their designation, given to them when they are created, or some affectation given to them by their owner. Often this affectation is a play on their designation. Occasionally, noteworthy droids will earn monikers based on their accomplishments.\n"   " <b>Designations (Names)</b>. BB-5 (Beebees), CH-33P (Cheep), OC-JK14 (Seejay), PT-7 (Poot), RG-G1 (G-G)</string>
    <string name="droid_class_2_traitsHeader">class 2 Droid Traits</string>
    <string name="droid_class_2_traitsText">As a class II droid, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Intelligence score increases by 2, and your Dexterity or Wisdom score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Droids don\'t age, though they require maintenance to retain functionality.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Droids tend toward no particular alignment. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Class II droids stand 2 to 4 feet tall and weigh about 70 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Small.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 25 feet.\n"   " <b>Type</b>. Your creature type is droid.\n"   " <b>Armor Integration</b>. You can not wear armor, but you can have the armor professionally integrated into your chassis over the course of a long rest. This work must be done by someone proficient with astrotech\'s implements. You must be proficient in armor in order to have it integrated. <b>Droid Resistances</b>. You are resistant to necrotic, poison, and psychic damage, and are immune to poison and disease. <b>Droid Systems</b>. You do not need to eat, drink, or breathe. Additionally, you no longer require a tech focus to cast tech powers. <b>Droid Vulnerabilities</b>. You are vulnerable to ion damage. Additionally, you have disadvantage on saving throws against effects that would deal ion or lightning damage. <b>Force-Insensitive</b>. While droids can be manipulated by many force powers, they can not sense the Force. You can not use force powers or take levels in forcecasting classes. <b>Integrated Engineering</b>. You have proficiency in one specialist\'s kit of your choice. The chosen kit is integrated into your chassis, and can not be removed while you are conscious. <b>Maintenance Mode</b>. Rather than sleep, you must spend 3 hours performing routine maintenance during a long rest to gain its benefits, during which you have disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it. <b>Rapid Reconstruction</b>. You are built with internal repair mechanisms. As a bonus action, you can choose to spend one of your Hit Dice to recover hit points. <b>Skill Protocol</b>. You have proficiency in two skills of your choice. <b>Undersized</b>. Your small stature makes it hard for you to wield bigger weapons. You can\'t use heavy shields. Additionally, you can\'t use martial weapons with the two-handed property unless it also has the light property, and if a martial weapon has the versatile property, you can only wield it in two hands. <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Binary. You can understand spoken and written Galactic Basic and one language of your choice, but you can not speak them.</string>
    <!--Droid class 3-->
    <string name="droid_class_3">DXoiD cLASS 3</string>
    <string name="droid_class_3_example">Droid class 3 Example</string>
    <string name="droid_class_3_info1">Class III droids are typically human-like in both shape and size, standing at around 6 feet. They are usually a polished metallic color, though this can vary based on tasks for which they are created, their affiliation, or quirks of their owner.\n"   " They are noteworthy for their slow, shuffling gait and typically overly talkative nature.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_3_info2">Class III droids are programmed to interact with humans. They are said to be the most advanced droids ever invented. Protocol, servant, tutor, and child care droids are all class III droids.\n"   " They are usually equipped with protocol chips which give them the cognitive functionality to engage socially.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_3_info3">Droids are typically called by their designation, given to them when they are created, or some affectation given to them by their owner. Often this affectation is a play on their designation. Occasionally, noteworthy droids will earn monikers based on their accomplishments.\n"   " <b>Designations (Names)</b>. K-OHN (Kone), I-5YQ (I-Five), O-MR1 (Omri), TC-14 (Teesee Fourteen)</string>
    <string name="droid_class_3_traitsHeader">class 3 Droid Traits</string>
    <string name="droid_class_3_traitsText">As a class III droid, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Charisma score increases by 2, and your Intelligence or Wisdom score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Droids don\'t age, though they require maintenance to retain functionality.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Droids tend toward no particular alignment. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Class III droids stand around the height of humans and weigh about 150 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 25 feet.\n"   " <b>Type</b>. Your creature type is droid.\n"   " <b>Armor Integration</b>. You can not wear armor, but you can have the armor professionally integrated into your chassis over the course of a long rest. This work must be done by someone proficient with astrotech\'s implements. You must be proficient in armor in order to have it integrated.\n"   " <b>Droid Resistances</b>. You are resistant to necrotic, poison, and psychic damage, and are immune to poison and disease.\n"   " <b>Droid Systems</b>. You do not need to eat, drink, or breathe. Additionally, you no longer require a tech focus to cast tech powers.\n"   " <b>Droid Vulnerabilities</b>. You are vulnerable to ion damage. Additionally, you have disadvantage on saving throws against effects that would deal ion or lightning damage.\n"   " <b>Force-Insensitive</b>. While droids can be manipulated by many force powers, they can not sense the Force. You can not use force powers or take levels in forcecasting classes.\n"   " <b>Knowledge Protocol</b>. You have proficiency in the Lore skill.\n"   " <b>Maintenance Mode</b>. Rather than sleep, you must spend 3 hours performing routine maintenance during a long rest to gain its benefits, during which you have disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it.\n"   " <b>Rapid Reconstruction</b>. You are built with internal repair mechanisms. As a bonus action, you can choose to spend one of your Hit Dice to recover hit points.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write all registered languages.</string>
    <!--Droid class 4-->
    <string name="droid_class_4">DXoiD cLASS 4</string>
    <string name="droid_class_4_example">Droid class 4 Example</string>
    <string name="droid_class_4_info1">Class IV droids are typically human-like in both shape and size, though there are many advanced models (such as droidekas) that forgo this standardization. They are usually colored to match their affiliation, though personally owned class IV droids might not be. Certain models of class IV droids, such as the HKseries, are made to look like class III droids to disguise their martial nature.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_4_info2">Class IV droids are programmed for military and security purposes. Such droids tend to perform tasks of violence or combat might be expected. Almost all class IV droids carry weapons. Armed combat droids are among the first droids ever created. Security, gladiator, battle, and assassin droids are all class IV droids.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_4_info3">Droids are typically called by their designation, given to them when they are created, or some affectation given to them by their owner. Often this affectation is a play on their designation. Occasionally, noteworthy droids will earn monikers based on their accomplishments.\n"   " <b>Designations (Names)</b>. K-2SO (Kay-Tuesso), PZ-99 (Peezee-Ninety-Nine), VL-44 (Vee-El Forty-Four)</string>
    <string name="droid_class_4_traitsHeader">class 4 Droid Traits</string>
    <string name="droid_class_4_traitsText">As a class IV droid, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Constitution score increases by 2, and your Strength or Dexterity score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Droids don\'t age, though they require maintenance to retain functionality.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Droids tend toward no particular alignment. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Class IV droids typically stand between 5 and 7 feet and weigh about 150 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Type</b>. Your creature type is droid. <b>Armor Integration</b>. You can not wear armor, but you can have the armor professionally integrated into your chassis over the course of a long rest. This work must be done by someone proficient with astrotech\'s implements. You must be proficient in armor in order to have it integrated.\n"   " <b>Droid Resistances</b>. You are resistant to necrotic, poison, and psychic damage, and are immune to poison and disease.\n"   " <b>Droid Systems</b>. You do not need to eat, drink, or breathe. Additionally, you no longer require a tech focus to cast tech powers.\n"   " <b>Droid Vulnerabilities</b>. You are vulnerable to ion damage. Additionally, you have disadvantage on saving throws against effects that would deal ion or lightning damage.\n"   " <b>Force-Insensitive</b>. While droids can be manipulated by many force powers, they can not sense the Force. You can not use force powers or take levels in forcecasting classes.\n"   " <b>Maintenance Mode</b>. Rather than sleep, you must spend 3 hours performing routine maintenance during a long rest to gain its benefits, during which you have disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it.\n"   " <b>Martial Protocol</b>. You have proficiency with light and medium armor as well as two simple or martial blasters or vibroweapons of your choice.\n"   " <b>Rapid Reconstruction</b>. You are built with internal repair mechanisms. As a bonus action, you can choose to spend one of your Hit Dice to recover hit points.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and one language of your choice. You can understand spoken and written Binary, but you can not speak it.</string>
    <!--Droid class 5-->
    <string name="droid_class_5">DXoiD cLASS 5</string>
    <string name="droid_class_5_example">Droid class 5 Example</string>
    <string name="droid_class_5_info1">Class V droids are typically vaguely human-like in both shape and size, standing at around 6 feet, although many can be larger. They are usually a polished metallic color, though this can vary based on tasks for which they are created, their affiliation, or quirks of their owner.\n"   " They are noteworthy for their simple programming and quiet, focused work habits.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_5_info2">Class V droids are programmed for menial and low-skill tasks. Such droids tend to perform basic tasks such as construction, lifting, maintenance, mining, sanitation, and transportation. Labor droids are fifth-degree droids.</string>
    <string name="droid_class_5_info3">Droids are typically called by their designation, given to them when they are created, or some affectation given to them by their owner. Often this affectation is a play on their designation. Occasionally, noteworthy droids will earn monikers based on their accomplishments.\n"   " <b>Designations (Names)</b>. CO-34 (See-Oh Three Four), FX-9 (Effex), PK-4 (Pook), SAE-B13 (Sable)</string>
    <string name="droid_class_5_traitsHeader">class 5 Droid Traits</string>
    <string name="droid_class_5_traitsText">As a class V droid, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Strength score increases by 2, and your Dexterity or Constitution score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Droids don\'t age, though they require maintenance to retain functionality.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Droids tend toward no particular alignment. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Class V droids typically stand between 5 and 7 feet and weigh around 260 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Type</b>. Your creature type is droid.\n"   " <b>Armor Integration</b>. You can not wear armor, but you can have the armor professionally integrated into your chassis over the course of a long rest. This work must be done by someone proficient with astrotech\'s implements. You must be proficient in armor in order to have it integrated.\n"   " <b>Droid Resistances</b>. You are resistant to necrotic, poison, and psychic damage, and are immune to poison and disease.\n"   " <b>Droid Systems</b>. You do not need to eat, drink, or breathe. Additionally, you no longer require a tech focus to cast tech powers.\n"   " <b>Droid Vulnerabilities</b>. You are vulnerable to ion damage. Additionally, you have disadvantage on saving throws against effects that would deal ion or lightning damage.\n"   " <b>Force-Insensitive</b>. While droids can be manipulated by many force powers, they can not sense the Force. You can not use force powers or take levels in forcecasting classes.\n"   " <b>Maintenance Mode</b>. Rather than sleep, you must spend 3 hours performing routine maintenance during a long rest to gain its benefits, during which you have disadvantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks. Additionally, if your long rest would be interrupted, you only need to complete the long rest instead of restarting it.\n"   " <b>Manual Laborer</b>. You have proficiency in Athletics and one set of artisan\'s implements of your choice.\n"   " <b>Powerful Build</b>. Your carrying capacity and the weight you can push, drag, or lift doubles. If it would already double, it instead triples.\n"   " <b>Rapid Reconstruction</b>. You are built with internal repair mechanisms. As a bonus action, you can choose to spend one of your Hit Dice to recover hit points.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Binary. You can understand spoken and written Galactic Basic and one language of your choice, but you can not speak it.</string>
    <!--Duros-->
    <string name="duros">DuXoS</string>
    <string name="duros_example">Duros Example</string>
    <string name="duros_info1">The duros are humanoids with smooth blue-green skin, red eyes, lipless mouths, long thin noseless faces and green blood. Olfactory organs beneath their eyes are responsible for their sense of smell. Both females and males are bald, though both genders are easily distinguished. Their large red goggle-like eyes have slit pupils. Duros females lay eggs as they are descended from ancient reptiles, and they are born in a larval grub stage. Unlike similar species, the duros take care of their offspring from birth.</string>
    <string name="duros_info2">Their home planet Duro is primarily uninhabited due to massive pollution on the world over time. Instead, it is covered with automated farms for food production. The duros live in twenty orbital space cities above the planet.\n"   " The duros also established a vast, grand starship construction industry in the Duro system. The duros set up their government around a consortium of starship construction corporations, with all important political decisions made by the stockholders of the corporations. This meant that any duros that held stock in a company could participate in the administration of the system.\n"   " With their strong memories, some duros also choose to become extraordinary storytellers, renowned galaxy-wide for their ability to learn a wide range of narratives by heart, and perform them all with stunning accuracy.</string>
    <string name="duros_info3">Duros names are generally melodic, with female names having softer intonations. Surnames are familial.</string>
    <string name="duros_traitsHeader">Duros Traits</string>
    <string name="duros_traitsText">As a duros, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, and your Intelligence score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Duros reach adulthood in their 20s and live an average of 150 years.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Duros tend toward no particular alignment. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Duros stand around 6 feet tall and weigh around 160 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. You have a keen eyesight, especially in the dark. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Galactic Traveler</b>. You have proficiency in the Piloting and Lore skills.\n"   " <b>Navigators</b>. You have proficiency in surveyor\'s implements.\n"   " <b>Superior Memory</b>. You can double your proficiency bonus for it when you make an Intelligence (Lore) check to recall information you have learned, or to recall the details of your experiences.\n"   " <b>Tech Resistance</b>. Growing up around technology leaves an impact on duros. You have advantage on Dexterity and Intelligence saving throws against tech powers.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Durese. Durese is a common interstellar tongue used by prominent spacers and traders.</string>
    <!--Ewok-->
    <string name="ewok">EWoK</string>
    <string name="ewok_example">Ewok Example</string>
    <string name="ewok_info1">Ewoks are sentient humanoid mammals, averaging about one meter in height, which can provide an advantage when trying to hide. They are covered in fur from head to toe, with brown and black the most common colors. Other Ewoks have near-white or reddish fur, but red fur is supposedly the rarest shade an Ewok can get. Most Ewoks have solid-colored fur, though a few sport stripes. Ewoks have large, bright eyes, small humanoid noses, and hands that possess two fingers and an opposable thumb. Despite their small size, Ewoks are physically strong enough to overpower combat-trained Humans. Their appearance has been likened to "little bears," though they are sometimes referred to as "mini Wookiees."</string>
    <string name="ewok_info2">Most Ewoks live high among the trees of the forest moon, in villages built between the closely spaced trees. The basic design of a tree village has a "Central Village" of thatched-roof huts on the primary limbs. These huts are high enough above the ground to be out of reach of predators. Suspended bridges connect the gaps between trees, adjoining distant huts. Knotted rope ladders allow access up or down.\n"   " Ewoks enjoy singing and playing music during celebrations and rituals. They are resourceful and tend to make use of everything they get their hands on; they use a variety of crude drums, horns, flutes, and other instruments in their music.</string>
    <string name="ewok_info3">Ewok names are comprised of growled consonants. Female names always end in a vowel. Surnames are clan-based.</string>
    <string name="ewok_traitsHeader">Ewok Traits</string>
    <string name="ewok_traitsText">As an Ewok, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, and your Constitution score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Ewoks reach adulthood in their early teens and live about 50 years.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Ewoks are inherently accepting, albeit naive, and tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Ewoks stand between 3 and 4 feet tall and weigh about 50 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Small.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 25 feet.\n"   " <b>Crude Weapon Specialists</b>. Ewoks are used to making do with less. You can spend 1 hour, which you can do over the course of a short rest, crafting a weapon out of loose materials. You can craft any simple kinetic weapon, but the weapon\'s damage suffers a -1 penalty.\n"   " <b>Keen Smell</b>. You have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks that rely on smell.\n"   " <b>Mask of the Wild</b>. You can attempt to hide even when you are only lightly obscured by foliage, heavy rain, falling snow, mist, and other natural phenomena. <b>Musical Culture</b>. Ewoks incorporate music in their celebrations and rituals. You have proficiency in an instrument of your choice.\n"   " <b>Natural Survivalist</b>. You have proficiency in Nature and Survival.\n"   " <b>Treeclimber</b>. You have a climbing speed of 25 feet. You have advantage on Strength saving throws and Strength (Athletics) checks that involve climbing.\n"   " <b>Undersized</b>. Your small stature makes it hard for you to wield bigger weapons. You can\'t use heavy shields. Additionally, you can\'t use martial weapons with the two-handed property unless it also has the light property, and if a martial weapon has the versatile property, you can only wield it in two hands.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Ewokese. You can understand spoken and written Galactic Basic, but your vocal cords do not allow you to speak it.</string>
    <!--Gamorrean-->
    <string name="gamorrean">GAMoXXEAN</string>
    <string name="gamorrean_example">Gamorrean Example</string>
    <string name="gamorrean_info1">Although a typical gamorrean is squat, green, and heavily built, not all shared these characteristics. Most gamorreans have a dark greenish coloration over a large portion of their bodies; however skin coloration does vary, particularly among females, with light skinned and two-toned pigmentation not uncommon. Black, brown, pinkish yellow, and even a rare white pigmentation are possible. Males tended to have less skin variation and had a greater tendency towards dark green skin perhaps because of their higher exposure to the radiation of the Gamorr Star. Eye coloration varied evenly between gold-yellow, blue, black and brown. The gamorreans generally put no importance on skin or eye coloration although there were some superstitions linked to certain markings.</string>
    <string name="gamorrean_info2">Gamorreans are organized into clans ruled by a male warlord and his wife, who was the most powerful of the clan matrons. While the warlord and his boars are solely concerned with preparing and participating in battle with rival clans, the matrons of the clan performed all the productive work including farming, hunting, manufacturing, and running businesses. Since the amount of available arable land on Gamorr is scarce, clans often lay claim to the same piece of land, and they spend their time fighting over possession.</string>
    <string name="gamorrean_info3">Gamorrean names are very gutteral and rough. Male names are typically one syllable while females are two. Surnames are based on clan affiliation rather than family.</string>
    <string name="gamorrean_traitsHeader">Gamorrean Traits</string>
    <string name="gamorrean_traitsText">As a gamorrean, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Strength score increases by 2, and your Constitution score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Gamorreans reach adulthood in their early teens and live no more than 70 years.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Gamorrean culture causes them to tend toward chaos, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Gamorreans typically stand between 5 and 6 feet tall and weigh up to 200 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet. <b>Gamorrean Toughness</b>. Your hit point maximum increases by 1, and it increases by 1 every time you gain a level. Additionally, you have advantage on Constitution saving throws.\n"   " <b>Gamorrean Weaponry</b>. You have proficiency with the vibroaxe, vibromace, and vibrosword.\n"   " <b>Savage Attacks</b>. When you score a critical hit with a melee weapon attack, you can roll one of the weapon\'s damage dice one additional time and add it to the extra damage of the critical hit.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Gamorrese. You can understand spoken and written Galactic Basic, but your vocal cords do not allow you to speak it. Gamorrese is characterized by its grunts and squeals, and its writing is a crude, pictographic style.</string>
    <!--Gungan-->
    <string name="gungan">GuNGAN</string>
    <string name="gungan_example">Gungan Example</string>
    <string name="gungan_info1">Starting life as tadpoles, Gungans develop into tall beings with extremely flexible cartilaginous skeletons. Strong leg muscles allow for powerful and quick frogkick style swimming through water as well as a remarkable jumping ability while on land. Fin-like ears (called haillu) also aid them in swimming, as well as expressing emotions like aggression, friendship, and fear. They have partially retractable eyestalks with nictitating membranes when underwater. Green eyes are unusual amongst Gungans.</string>
    <string name="gungan_info2">Gungans are generally a generous and peaceful species. They truly love to have visitors and warmly welcome them; however, they would remain suspicious until the visitors have earned their respect. Gungans are not tolerant of anyone who threatens their peaceful culture. They have very strict laws, and will go to the extremes to punish anyone who has committed a minor crime. Vandals, for example, can be given a sentence of exile, caning, or even stoning.\n"   " If a Gungan is cast out of society, it is very difficult for them to return. If they do manage to return legally, they are often subjected to heavy discrimination. This can make life very difficult for them and can go on for months or years, until their past offenses disappear from memory. Returning back to the settlement they were exiled from illegally will sometimes result in the death penalty, especially if they brought along outsiders.</string>
    <string name="gungan_info3">Gungan names are often repeated syllables hyphenated.</string>
    <string name="gungan_traitsHeader">Gungan Traits</string>
    <string name="gungan_traitsText">As a Gungan, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, and your Strength score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Gungans reach adulthood in their early teens and live about 70 years.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Gungans tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Gungans typically stand 6 to 7 feet tall and weigh about 170 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Amphibious</b>. You can breathe air and water.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Accustomed to life underwater, you have superior vision in low light conditions. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Flexible</b>. You have advantage on Dexterity (Acrobatics) checks that involve flexibility.\n"   " <b>Heat Sensitivity</b>. You have disadvantage on Constitution saving throws made to avoid exhaustion due to extreme heat.\n"   " <b>Martial Proficiency</b>. You have proficiency with light and medium armor as well as the techstaff and vibropike.\n"   " <b>Strong-Legged</b>. When you make a long jump, you can cover a number of feet up to twice your Strength score. When you make a high jump, you can leap a number of feet up into the air equal to 3 + twice your Strength modifier.\n"   " <b>Swim</b>. You have a swimming speed of 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Gungan. When speaking Galactic Basic, you often have trouble with word tenses and infinitives; this usually has a comical effect.</string>
    <!--Human-->
    <string name="human">HuMAN</string>
    <string name="human_example">Human Example</string>
    <string name="human_info1">Humans are an intelligent species that originated on Coruscant, but can be found on many other planets across the galaxy, including Naboo, Tatooine, and Alderaan. They come in two sexes, male and female, and give birth to live young. They are bipedal beings with a bilateral symmetry, having a front and a back end, as well as an upside and downside. Their bodies are comprised of a torso with a head and four limbs attached to it. The upper limbs, or arms, end in hands which had five fingers each; the lower ones, called legs, end in feet. The human fingers have multiple points of articulation, and one of them is an opposable thumb that allowed for fine manipulation. Finally, they have one head perched atop their torso. Many other species, including twi\'leks, mon calamari, or zabraks, are referred to as "humanoids" because of their structural resemblance to humans.</string>
    <string name="human_info2">Humans can occupy a variety of employs, from politicians to bounty hunters, swoop racers, smugglers, or even a farmer. There exist many planetary groups of humans with their own cultures, such as the Alderaanians or the Pamarthens. Humans are the most populous species in the Galaxy.</string>
    <string name="human_info3">Humans are the most populace species in the Galaxy, and thus their names vary drastically based on the planet or culture with whom they reside.</string>
    <string name="human_traitsHeader">Human Traits</string>
    <string name="human_traitsText">As a human, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. One ability score of your choice increases by 2, and two other ability scores of your choice increase by 1. Alternatively, four ability scores of your choice each increase by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Humans reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Humans tend toward no particular alignment. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Humans vary widely in height and build, from barely 5 feet to well over 6 feet tall. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Defiant</b>. Humans are known to be stubborn and often refuse to give up, even against the worst odds. When you or a creature you can see that can see and understand you makes an ability check, attack roll, or saving throw, you can roll a d4 and add it to their roll (no action required). Once you\'ve used this feature, you must complete a short or long rest before you can use it again.\n"   " <b>Human Versatility</b>. You gain proficiency in one skill, one tool, and one weapon of your choice. <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and one extra language of your choice. Humans typically learn the languages of other peoples they deal with, including obscure dialects. They are fond of sprinkling their speech with words borrowed from other tongues: trandoshan curses, twi\'lek musical expressions, chiss military phrases, and so on.</string>
    <!--Ithorian-->
    <string name="ithorian">iTHoXiAN</string>
    <string name="ithorian_example">Ithorian Example</string>
    <string name="ithorian_info1">Ithorians have two mouths and four throats, allowing them to speak in stereo. Female Ithorians have two humps on the back of their head, while males have only one. They have glossy, usually brown flesh. Their reflexes and coordination are somewhat slower than that of average humanoids.\n"   " In addition to allowing them to speak their unique stereophonic language, the Ithorians\' four throats also have the ability to violently expel air, resulting in a deafening and potentially concussive scream. Despite this fact, most Ithorians go their entire lives without ever resorting to violence, and so the ability remained relatively ambiguous.</string>
    <string name="ithorian_info2">Ithorians worship the "Mother Jungle," a spiritual entity embodying the lush, tropical ecology of their world, Ithor. They are generally devoted environmentalists, staunch herbivores, and complete pacifists, devoting much time to contemplating their ecology, studying plants and their uses and the overall respecting of all living things. Most Ithorians never set foot on their own planet, instead living in floating cities above their world called herdships. Only three of their continents have been explored and harvested, the other two never having been touched by Ithorian hands. They demonstrate extreme belief in the protection and sustaining of their environment as dictated by their "Law of Life."</string>
    <string name="ithorian_info3">Ithorian names are quite varied in length but most names are soft and melodic. They are often difficult to prounounce by other species, so many Ithorians adopt nicknames.</string>
    <string name="ithorian_traitsHeader">ithorian Traits</string>
    <string name="ithorian_traitsText">As an Ithorian, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Charisma score increases by 2, and your Wisdom score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Ithorians reach adulthood in their late teens and live an average of 85 years.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Ithorians tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Shorter Ithorians stand around 6 feet while taller reach over 7 and a half. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Call for Peace</b>. As an action on your turn, you can emphatically demand that your foes embrace peace, thereby distracting them. Until the end of your next turn, enemies within 10 feet of you that can see you gain disadvantage on attack rolls against your allies. Once you use this trait, you can\'t use it again until you finish a short or long rest.\n"   " <b>Hold Breath</b>. Ithorians have a great lung capacity and can hold their breath for up to 15 minutes at a time.\n"   " <b>Law of Life</b>. Ithorians have a sacred respect for the natural world, taking great care to preserve and study it. You have proficiency in the Nature skill and the bioanalysis kit.\n"   " <b>Sonic Scream</b>. As an action, you can violently expel air in a 15-foot cone. When you do so, each creature in the area of the exhalation must make a Wisdom saving throw (DC = 8 + your proficiency bonus + your Constitution modifier). A creature takes 2d6 sonic damage on a failed save, and half as much damage on a successful one. The damage increases to 4d6 at 5th level, 6d6 at 11th level, and 8d6 at 17th level. This ability has no effect on constructs. You can use this feature a number of times equal to your proficiency bonus. You regain all expended uses when you complete a long rest.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Ithorese. You can understand spoken and written Galactic Basic, but your vocal cords do not allow you to speak it.</string>
    <!--Jawa-->
    <string name="jawa">JAWA</string>
    <string name="jawa_example">Jawa Example</string>
    <string name="jawa_info1">Jawas are easily identifiable by their traditional brown hooded robes, though it is not unheard of for them to wear other colors. Other notable features included their glowing yellow eyes, small stature and high pitched, quickly spoken language called Jawaese. Underneath their robes, jawas appear to be gaunt, rodent-like creatures, with shrunken faces and yellow eyes.</string>
    <string name="jawa_info2">Jawas are a communal, compulsive scavenger species who spend most of their life devoted to scavenging the deserts of Tatooine in search of any scrap metal, droid or mechanical part left behind from millennia of star travel and technological advancement. Most non-jawas regard the jawas as scavengers and thieves, a description that most jawas actually find pleasing.\n"   " The jawa\'s unofficial motto is not to look for uses in a salvaged item, but rather to imagine someone else who might find a use for it. This is evidenced in their endless search for wares with which to trade with almost any being jawas encounter. They have a kind of instinctive feel for machinery and electronics, notorious for knowing how to get a piece of equipment functioning just well enough to sell.</string>
    <string name="jawa_info3">Jawa names are quickly spoken, complex, and often misunderstood. Jawas who spend the majority of their time around other species respond well to nicknames. Male and female names do not significantly deviate. Surnames are clan based.</string>
    <string name="jawa_traitsHeader">Jawa Traits</string>
    <string name="jawa_traitsText">As a jawa, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, and your Intelligence score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Jawas are considered adults when they make their first sale and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Jawas tendency to steal and swindle causes them to tend towards the dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Jawas stand around 3 to 4 feet tall and weigh about 40 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Small.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 25 feet. <b>Darkvision</b>. You have a keen eyesight, especially in the dark. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Grovel, Cower, and Beg</b>. As an action on your turn, you can cower pathetically to distract nearby foes. Until the end of your next turn, your allies gain advantage on attack rolls against enemies within 10 feet of you that can see you. Once you use this trait, you can’t use it again until you finish a short or long rest.\n"   " <b>Heat Adaptation</b>. You have advantage on Constitution saving throws made to avoid exhaustion due to extreme heat.\n"   " <b>Tech Dabbler</b>. You know the ion blast at-will tech power. When you reach 3rd level, you learn and can cast the repair droid tech power once per long rest. When you reach 5th level, you learn and can cast the hold droid tech power once per long rest. Your techcasting ability is Intelligence. You do not require use of a wristpad for these powers.\n"   " <b>Thieving</b>. You have proficiency in the Sleight of Hand skill. <b>Tinker</b>. You have proficiency with tinker’s implements. You can use these and spend 1 hour and 100 cr worth of materials to construct a Tiny Device (AC 5, 1 hp). You can take the Use an Object action to have your device cause one of the following effects: create a small explosion, create a repeating loud noise for 1 minute, create smoke for 1 minute, cause a small electrical fire. You can maintain a number of these devices up to your proficiency bonus at once, and a device stops functioning after 24 hours away from you. You can dismantle the device to reclaim the materials used to create it.\n"   " <b>Undersized</b>. Your small stature makes it hard for you to wield bigger weapons. You can’t use heavy shields. Additionally, you can’t use martial weapons with the two-handed property unless it also has the light property, and if a martial weapon has the versatile property, you can only wield it in two hands. <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Jawaese (and the Jawa Trade Language). You can understand spoken and written Galactic Basic, but your vocal cords do not allow you to speak it. Jawaese blends quickly spoken, semi-meaningless syllables with scents to be understood. To more easily bargain and trade with other species, they rely on a simplified variant called the Jawa Trade language which removes the use of scent.</string>
    <!--Kel Dor-->
    <string name="kel_dor">KEL DoX</string>
    <string name="kel_dor_example">Kel Dor Example</string>
    <string name="kel_dor_info1">Due to Dorin having a unique atmosphere composed of helium and a gas unique to their world, the kel dors are forced to wear an antiox breath mask and protective goggles whenever in atmospheres of a different composition. Without their protective goggles, kel dors were considered effectively blind when away from Dorin. They were also able to survive in the vacuum of space for a short time, though it was unknown exactly how long they could withstand it.\n"   " The kel dors also have heightened reflexes, a result of the extrasensory organs in their heads. They are typically quick and wise.</string>
    <string name="kel_dor_info2">Kel dors are noted for their simple approach to justice, and they typically see moral issues in black and white. On the one hand, the kel dor are noted for their hospitality; they would never turn away a stranger in need. Yet, kel dors are not averse to taking the law into their own hands, and have no compunctions about putting to death a thief who was merely stealing to feed himself.\n"   " Kel dor Force-sensitives are often trained as Baran Do Sages, who have an honored place in kel dor culture. They often serve as advisers to rich and powerful kel dor families. Wars and disasters have been averted simply by the insight of a Baran Do Sage.</string>
    <string name="kel_dor_info3">Kel dor names are base on sound generated by Dorin\'s unique atmosphere. Surnames are based on ancient family trades.</string>
    <string name="kel_dor_traitsHeader">Kel Dor Traits</string>
    <string name="kel_dor_traitsText">As a kel dor, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Wisdom score increases by 2, and your Dexterity score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Kel dor reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Kel dors\' structured nature causes them to tend toward lawful balanced, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Kel dor typically stand around 6 feet tall and weigh about 160 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Your natural evolution allows you to see what others do not in dim and dark conditions. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can\'t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Foreign Biology</b>. You cannot breathe oxygen. The kel dors have created a breathing apparatus to negate the negative effects of living in an oxygen rich environment, but if your mask is removed while you are in such an environment, you lose consciousness.\n"   " <b>Life in the Void</b>. You have resistance to necrotic damage, and while exposed to the vacuum of space, you can survive for a number of hours equal to your Constitution modifier (minimum 1 hour), instead of a number of rounds.\n"   " <b>Telepathy</b>. You can communicate telepathically with creatures within 30 feet of you. You must share a language with the target in order to communicate in this way.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Kel Dor.</string>
    <!--Mon Calamari-->
    <string name="mon_calamari">MoN cALAMAXi</string>
    <string name="mon_calamari_example">Mon Calamari Example</string>
    <string name="mon_calamari_info1">The mon calamari are a bipedal, amphibious species with high-domed heads, webbed hands and large, goggle-like eyes. In addition to being webbed, the mon calamari hand presents three suction-cup like holes on its palm, and featured five claw-tipped fingers: one opposable thumb, two long middle fingers, and two very short outer fingers. Although they are shaped like flippers, their feet can nevertheless fit into boots designed for human-like feet. The females are distinguished from the males by their more prominent chest areas.</string>
    <string name="mon_calamari_info2">The mon calamari have developed a very advanced and civilized culture. Their art, music, literature, and science show a creativity surpassed by few in the galaxy. Mon calamari literature depicts stars as islands in a galactic sea, showing a passionate longing to explore space and discover other civilizations. Mon Calamari are both soft-spoken and gentle, slow to anger, and have the remarkable ability to maintain their concentration without being distracted by emotional responses. They are both inquisitive and creative, and have a near-legendary quality of being both determined and dedicated; once a mon calamari decides on a course of action, they are not easily swayed from that decision. They often fixate themselves on "lost causes."</string>
    <string name="mon_calamari_info3">Mon calamari names generally have a melodic feel.</string>
    <string name="mon_calamari_traitsHeader">Mon Calamari Traits</string>
    <string name="mon_calamari_traitsText">As a mon calamari, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Charisma score increases by 2, and your Intelligence or Wisdom score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Mon calamari reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Mon calamaris\' love of the arts cause them to tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Mon calamari stand between 5 and 6 feet tall and rarely weigh more than 150 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet. <b>Amphibious</b>. You can breathe air and water.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Accustomed to life underwater, you have superior vision in low light conditions. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can\'t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Mon Calamari Resistance</b>. You have advantage on saving throws against effects that grant the slowed condition and you have resistance against cold damage (explained in chapter 9).\n"   " <b>Musical</b>. You have proficiency in one musical instrument of your choice.\n"   " <b>Swim</b>. You have a swimming speed of 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic, Mon Cal, and one language of your choice.</string>
    <!--Nautolan-->
    <string name="nautolan">NAuToLAN</string>
    <string name="nautolan_example">Nautolan Example</string>
    <string name="nautolan_info1">Nautolans possess physiology common to amphibious species, including low light vision and excellent swimming skills. Their bony endoskeleton and dense cartilage make them tough and resistant to glancing blows. An egg-laying species, Nautolans emerge from their egg as a tadpole that develops arms, legs, and head-tails during their second year of life. Roughly the same size as a Human infant during this time, their limbs are weak and unable to support their weight, forcing youthful Nautolans to remain in aquatic environments for much of their childhood.</string>
    <string name="nautolan_info2">The society developed by the Nautolans on Glee Anselm is centralized around local families and governments. The centralized government of Glee Anselm is comprised of representatives from the Council of Elders that govern each settlement. Elders are elected on merit, and can be made up of youthful politicians as well as the most aged members of the society. A culture that promotes life-long mates, Nautolan families are characterized by their loyalty between spouses and the equality of the sexes in the household. Arranged marriages are not uncommon.\n"   " No cultural affinity for the Force ever developed on Glee Anselm, though members of the Nautolan species recognize its importance and respected those among them that were Forceful.</string>
    <string name="nautolan_info3">Nautolan names are generally short and melodic. Female names usually end in a vowel. Surnames are familial.</string>
    <string name="nautolan_traitsHeader">Nautolan Traits</string>
    <string name="nautolan_traitsText">As a Nautolan, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, and your Wisdom score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Nautolans reach adulthood in their early teens and live about 70 years on average.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Nautolans\' benevolence cause them to tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Nautolans typically stand 5 to 6 feet tall and rarely weigh more than 160 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Acute Smell</b>. Whenever you make a Wisdom (Perception) check involving smell, you are considered to have expertise in the Perception skill.\n"   " <b>Amphibious</b>. You can breathe air and water.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Accustomed to life underwater, you have superior vision in low light conditions. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Hide</b>. You have a thick hide. While you are unarmored or wearing light armor, your AC is 12 + your Dexterity modifier.\n"   " <b>Natural Empathy</b>. Nautolan head tentacles are adept at determining moods. You have advantage on Wisdom (Insight) checks to determine emotions against humanoids and beasts within 10 feet of you.\n"   " <b>Swim</b>. You have a swimming speed of 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Nautila. Nautila is unique in that it can only be properly pronounced underwater due to its use of pheromones in addition to spoken sounds. In any other environment, the language loses a great amount of detail that nautolans find annoying.</string>
    <!--Rodian-->
    <string name="rodian">XoDiAN</string>
    <string name="rodian_example">Rodian Example</string>
    <string name="rodian_info1">The rodians are green-skinned humanoids from the planet Rodia. They possess distinctive faces: large, round, multifaceted eyes; tapir-like snouts; and a pair of saucer-shaped antennae on their heads, which served to detect vibrations. The flexible snouts augmented the rodians\' finely tuned olfactory senses, collecting and filtering the air. Their characteristically large eyes indicated a primarily nocturnal ancestry and were capable of seeing into the infrared part of the spectrum. Due to their love of fighting and active lifestyles, most rodians kept in good condition, normally lean and wiry; however, some wealthy rodians became complacent and obese.</string>
    <string name="rodian_info2">Rodian culture is obsessed with violence and death, due to behaviors and practices that are ingrained since their earliest ancestry. Their densely packed jungle homeworld is ill-suited for agriculture, requiring rodians to compete with vicious predators for most of their food, some of which can wipe out entire rodian villages. As the rodians developed cunning hunting tactics to survive, the hunt became central to their culture. Eventually, having driven most of the other predators on the planet to near extinction, they began to hunt each other in various wars and gladiatorial contests.</string>
    <string name="rodian_info3">Female names tend to be longer than male names. Surnames are familial.</string>
    <string name="rodian_traitsHeader">Xodian Traits</string>
    <string name="rodian_traitsText">As a rodian, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Dexterity score increases by 2, and your Constitution score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Rodians reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Rodian culture\'s violent focus causes them to tend toward the dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Rodians typically stand 5 to 6 feet tall and weigh 160 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet. Adept Climbers. You have a climbing speed of 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Your vision can easily cut through darkness. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Keen Hearing and Smell</b>. You have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks that involve hearing or smell.\n"   " <b>Stalking Hunter</b>. You have proficiency in the Survival and Stealth skills.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Rodese. Rodians can communicate with each other using pheromones. Force-sensitives can detect this communication, though they can’t understand it.</string>
    <!--Sith Pureblood-->
    <string name="sith_pureblood">SiTH PuXEBLooD</string>
    <string name="sith_pureblood_example">Sith Pureblood Example</string>
    <string name="sith_pureblood_info1">Sith are a proud and violent species of humanoids that evolved on Korriban, a planet within the Horuset system in an isolated Outer Rim region called the Stygian Caldera. Sith have a larger than average number of individuals with potential to use the Force in their species, so high in fact that the entire species was considered strongly Force-sensitive.\n"   " Sith purebloods are characterized by their expressive facial appendages, bone spurs, cranial horns, and predatory gaze.</string>
    <string name="sith_pureblood_info2">Sith culture is a rigid and stratified caste-based society. For the sith, war and violence are just as much a part of the natural order of life as peace or serenity. Though they are in an almost constant state of war, their civilization is quite sophisticated; they see these acts not as cruel or barbaric, but simply basic aspects of existence. Their constant warring led to a dwindling of the population on their original homeworld of Korriban as well as cultivated an intensely xenophobic society.</string>
    <string name="sith_pureblood_info3">Sith pureblood names are not conventional. They are often named for virtues in the Sith tongue. Sith rarely share surnames, since they do not value family ties. When a sith pureblood achieves a success or victory, they often change their name to match their perceived newfound status. Since Force-sensitivity is common in sith purebloods, and their culture is built around strength, most sith are called simply "My Lord," or some other epithet, by their underlings.</string>
    <string name="sith_pureblood_traitsHeader">Sith Pureblood Traits</string>
    <string name="sith_pureblood_traitsText">As a sith pureblood, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Charisma score increases by 2, and your Strength or Dexterity score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Sith reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. The cruelty of the Sith causes them to tend toward chaotic dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Sith generally stand between 5 and 6 feet tall and weigh less than 200 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Your vision can easily cut through darkness. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Force-Sensitive</b>. You know the denounce at-will force power. When you reach 3rd level, you learn and can cast the curse force power once per long rest. When you reach 5th level, you learn and can cast the bestow curse force power once per long rest. Your forcecasting ability is Charisma for these powers.\n"   " <b>Keen Senses</b>. You have proficiency in the Perception skill. Menacing. You have proficiency in the Intimidation skill.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Sith. Sith is an agglutinative language, in which words or even phrases were made up of linears sequences of distinct meaningful units.</string>
    <!--Togruta-->
    <string name="togruta">ToGXuTA</string>
    <string name="togruta_example">Togruta Example</string>
    <string name="togruta_info1">Togruta have rusty skin tones ranging in hue from blue to red to green, with white pigmentation on their faces, greyish lips, and white stripes adorn various parts of their bodies. The pattern of stripes varies from individual to individual. This red and white pattern was a phenotype left over from their ancestor\'s camouflage that helped them to blend in with Shili\'s natural surroundings.\n"   " Their heads bear two montrals, with three to four head-tails, whose stripes were darker than those of the montrals. Togruta have the ability to sense the proximity and movement of physical objects around them by means of their hollow montrals, which detect space ultrasonically. Young togrutas\' montrals and posterior head-tail do not fully grow until adolescence, when their montrals curve and their final head-tail grows to the length of their other head-tails.</string>
    <string name="togruta_info2">Togruta have a strong sense of unity and togetherness. On their native homeworld of Shili, they rely on each other and band together to take a stand against the massive monsters that hunt them. The creatures of Shili most often attack in groups, which was even more reason for the native togruta to work together. While most of Shili is covered in the scrublands where the togruta hunt their herbivorous prey, the togruta live in small communities in the forest valleys.</string>
    <string name="togruta_info3">Togruta names are typically long. Surnames are familial.</string>
    <string name="togruta_traitsHeader">Togruta Traits</string>
    <string name="togruta_traitsText">As a togruta, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Wisdom score increases by 2, and your Strength or Dexterity score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Togruta reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Togruta culture focuses on unity which causes them to tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Togruta typically stand between 5 and 6 feet tall and weigh 150 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Mask of the Wild</b>. You can attempt to hide even when you are only lightly obscured by foliage, heavy rain, falling snow, mist, and other natural phenomena.\n"   " <b>Montral Reception</b>. You have tremorsense out to 30 feet. You can detect and pinpoint the origin of vibrations within a specific radius, provided that you and the source of the vibrations are in contact with the same ground or substance. Tremorsense can’t be used to detect flying or incorporeal creatures.\n"   " <b>Wild Hunters</b>. You have proficiency in the Survival skill. <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Togruti. Togruti is an ornate language characterized by trills and long vowel sounds which are modified by subtle tremors in the togruta’s head-tails. This language is heavily influenced by Basic, but also incorporates some native idioms, which cause Basic-speaking togruta to use seemingly strange expressions.</string>
    <!--Trandoshan-->
    <string name="trandoshan">TXANDoSHAN</string>
    <string name="trandoshan_example">Trandoshan Example</string>
    <string name="trandoshan_info1">Trandoshans are a large, bipedal sentient species, with scaly skin which was shed roughly once every standard year and was thought to be very durable. Cold-blooded reptiles, trandoshans had two super-sensitive varied color eyes with horizontal black pupils, which could see far into the infrared range. Each of their four limbs ends in three razor sharp claws. These are perfect for combat, but did not grant them manual dexterity, making a trandoshan\'s finger movements somewhat clumsy and awkward.</string>
    <string name="trandoshan_info2">Trandoshans worship their goddess, the Scorekeeper, whom they would appease through acts which increased their Jagannath points. This is done by living a lifestyle which was, by non-trandoshan standards, overtly aggressive, leading many trandoshans to become bounty hunters, mercenaries, or slavers. Trandoshans especially prize wookiee pelts, which consequently play a large part in earning Jagannath points-capturing the pelts of particularly infamous wookiees would give the hunter a large increase in Jagganath points. To be shamed or captured during a hunt would zero one\'s Jagganath points-effectively making their life forfeit in the eyes of the Scorekeeper. They could, however, win all those points back by killing the one who zeroed their score.</string>
    <string name="trandoshan_info3">Trandoshan names are quite harsh and contain a lot of elongated sounds, as well as a lot of s\'s. Differences between male and female names are often very subtle, but there is a higher chance for female names to contain softer sounds.</string>
    <string name="trandoshan_traitsHeader">Trandoshan Traits</string>
    <string name="trandoshan_traitsText">As a trandoshan, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Strength score increases by 2, and your Wisdom score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Trandoshans reach adulthood in their early teens and rarely live to be older than 70.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Trandoshans tend toward the dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Trandoshans stand as tall as 7 and a half feet and can weigh over 300 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Claws</b>. Your claws are natural weapons, which you can use to make unarmed strikes. Additionally, your unarmed strikes deal 1d4 kinetic damage.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Your vision can easily cut through darkness. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Hide</b>. You have a thick hide. While you are unarmored or wearing light armor, your AC is 12 + your Dexterity modifier.\n"   " <b>Regenerative</b>. When you take damage, you can use your reaction and expend a Hit Die to regain hit points as long as the damage would not reduce your hit points to 0.\n"   " <b>Saving Face</b>. Trandoshans are careful not to show weakness in front of their allies, for fear of losing status. If you miss with an attack roll or fail an ability check or a saving throw, you can gain a bonus to the roll equal to the number of allies you can see within 30 feet of you (maximum bonus of +5). Once you use this trait, you can’t use it again until you finish a short or long rest.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Dosh. Dosh is characterized by its harsh grunts, hisses and growls, and its written form that used alphabetic glyphs.</string>
    <!--Tusken-->
    <string name="tusken">TuSKEN</string>
    <string name="tusken_example">Tusken Example</string>
    <string name="tusken_info1">While Tuskens, also known as Tusken Raiders or Sand People, are easily recognizable by their full-body clothing, goggles, and mouth filters, little of their true physical appearance can be discerned. From birth, Tuskens are covered in wraps, and, barring very rare occasions, will not bare any part of their skin in sight of another person. This, combined with their hostility to outsiders and Tatooine\'s remote and arid nature, makes even study of Tusken corpses difficult.</string>
    <string name="tusken_info2">Tuskens are a primative, tribal race, mostly living in small clans scattered throughout Tatooine\'s deserts. Due to the harsh and unforgiving desert environment, Tusken clans are often xenophobic and territorial, but it is not unknown for them to adopt members of other species into the clan. They believe that all water is sacred and promised to them alone, and are infamous among the other residents of Tatooine for raiding and pillaging settlements and farms.\n"   " Tusken clans are usually very stratified, with males as hunters and warriors, while females and children maintain the camp. Tusken warriors hold their bond with their gaderffii weapons and Bantha mounts as sacred, and will choose death before relinquishing either.</string>
    <string name="tusken_info3">Tusken naming traditions vary between clans, but most are made up of harsh, guttural sounds. Tuskens do not use surnames.</string>
    <string name="tusken_traitsHeader">Tusken Traits</string>
    <string name="tusken_traitsText">As a Tusken, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Constitution score increases by 2, and your Strength or Charisma score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Tuskens are considered adults when they turn 15. Because of the harsh and unforgiving climate of their home world, they rarely live longer than half a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Tusken culture\'s violent focus and disregard of those outside the tribe causes them to tend towards chaotic dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Tusken stand between 5 and 6 feet tall and weigh around 155 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Aggressive</b>. As a bonus action, you can move up to your speed toward an enemy of your choice that you can see or hear. You must end this move closer to the enemy than you started.\n"   " <b>Animal Handler</b>. You have proficiency in the Animal Handling skill.\n"   " <b>Desert Protection</b>. You have advantage on saving throws against being blinded. <b>Fearsome Roar</b>. Once per day, you can cast the fear force power. Charisma is your forcecasting ability for this power.\n"   " <b>Survivors of the Sands</b>. You have proficiency in the Survival skill. Additionally, you don’t treat desert terrain as difficult terrain. Lastly, you have advantage on Constitution saving throws made to avoid exhaustion due to extreme heat.\n"   " <b>Tech-Impaired</b>. While tuskens can figure out basic technology, they experience difficulty using more complex equipment like wristpads. You can not use tech powers or take levels in techcasting classes.\n"   " <b>Tusken Weaponry</b>. You have proficiency with the cycler rifle and vibroaxe.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak Tusken, and speak, read, and write Galactic Basic. Tusken is a guttural language characterized by its barks, growls, and roars. While Tuskens typically understand Galactic Basic, it is rare to hear them speak anything but Tusken. Tusken has no written form. Tuskens also know a complex sign language used to communicate with other tuskens silently.</string>
    <!--Twi'Lek-->
    <string name="twilek">TWi\'LEK</string>
    <string name="twilek_example">Twi\'lek Example</string>
    <string name="twilek_info1">Twi\'leks are usually thin, although corpulent individuals were known to exist. Twi\'leks are omnivores; this diet is essential given that food is scarce on their homeworld, Ryloth. Twi\'leks possess multiple stomachs, an unusual trait that enables them to eat almost any food. When traveling off their homeworld, twi\'leks rarely refuse food, which frequently leads to obesity among starfarers. Twi\'lek society also considers obesity as a sign of influence and success.</string>
    <string name="twilek_info2">The natural grace and exotic beauty of the female twi\'leks make them a popular target among slave traders. Slavery is the main currency of Ryloth. Some see it as a chance to make money by kidnapping or selling orphaned children, while others see slavery as a way of saving children from growing up in Ryloth\'s harsh environment. A number of twi\'leks believe that slavery is an efficient way to proliferate their species and preserve their culture, as the twi\'leks lack their own means of inter-planetary travel. Regardless of how it came about, many twi\'leks live as slaves or entertainers and are considered status symbols, especially the females of rarer skin hues. Twi\'leks that manage to escape from captivity usually turned to a life of thievery or prostitution, with both genders making use of their powers of seduction.</string>
    <string name="twilek_info3">Twi\'lek names combine their first name and a clan name into a single name, rather than having a separate surname.</string>
    <string name="twilek_traitsHeader">Twi\'lek Traits</string>
    <string name="twilek_traitsText">As a twi\'lek, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Charisma score increases by 2, and your Dexterity score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Twi\'leks reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Twi\'leks harsh upbringing cause them to tend toward the dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Twi\'leks stand between 5 and 7 feet tall and weigh up to 200 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Charismatic</b>. You have proficiency with Deception or Persuasion (your choice).\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Your vision can easily cut through darkness. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Elegant Dancers</b>. You have proficiency in the Performance skill.\n"   " <b>Natural Antitoxins</b>. You have advantage on saving throws against poison and disease, and you have resistance against poison damage (explained in Chapter 9).\n"   " <b>Unarmed Combatant</b>. Your unarmed strikes deal 1d4 kinetic damage and have the finesse property.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Twi’leki. You can communicate non-verbally with other twi’leks through a complex language of subtle head-tail motions.</string>
    <!--Weequay-->
    <string name="weequay">WEEquAy</string>
    <string name="weequay_example">Weequay Example</string>
    <string name="weequay_info1">Weequays are humanoids with thick, leathery skin that ranges in color from tan to dark brown. Their faces are lipless, with a frill along each of their jowls.</string>
    <string name="weequay_info2">Weequays have the ability to communicate with members of their own clan through smell by exuding complex pheromones. This pheromonal language can not be understood by any other species, or even by Weequays of another clan. Only Jedi senses can even tell that two Weequay are communicating. Since each Weequay\'s pheromones are unique, Weequay have no need for a name within their clan. As a result, speech is only a secondary form of communication for Weequay, and they seldom speak a whole sentence, resulting in Humans mistakenly believing the species to be unintelligent.\n"   " Male Weequay often tie their hair into a long braid each year spent away from their homeworld as a tribute to their home. When they returned, they shaved their braids. Weequays serving the Hutts were often very close to their homeworld, and would only have one or two braids. Female Weequay were usually bald, and did not follow this tradition.</string>
    <string name="weequay_info3">Only Weequay who have to live among other clans, or among non-Weequay, take a personal name. Even then, some are simply referred to as "Weequay". In Weequay culture, individual identity is much less important than the clan. As long as the clan survives, a single Weequay is expendable. This results in a sometimes brutal culture.</string>
    <string name="weequay_traitsHeader">Weequay Traits</string>
    <string name="weequay_traitsText">As a weequay, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Constitution score increases by 2, and your Wisdom or Charisma score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Weequay reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Weequay ruthlessness and greed cause them to tend toward chaotic dark side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Weequay typically stand about 6 feet tall and weigh 150 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Keen Smell</b>. You have advantage on Wisdom (Perception) checks that rely on smell.\n"   " <b>Savage Attacks</b>. When you score a critical hit with a melee weapon attack, you can roll one of the weapon’s damage dice one additional time and add it to the extra damage of the critical hit.\n"   " <b>Tanned</b>. You have tough, leathery skin. While you are unarmored or wearing light armor, your AC is 13 + your Dexterity modifier. Additionally, You have advantage on Constitution saving throws made to avoid exhaustion due to extreme heat.\n"   " <b>Weapon Training</b>. You have proficiency in two vibroweapons or blasters of your choice.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Sriluurian. You can communicate with other Weequay within 30 feet without speaking through use of pheromones. Force attuned individuals can detect the communication but can’t understand it.</string>
    <!--Wookie-->
    <string name="wookie">WooKiE</string>
    <string name="wookie_example">Wookie Example</string>
    <string name="wookie_info1">Wookiees are a tall species of furry giants from the planet Kashyyyk, who can grow to a height of over eight feet. They are covered from head to toe in a thick, shaggy coat of hair with water-shedding properties that notably came in shades of brown, black, gray, and white. The species has two sexes, female and male. The latter grows long beards in adult life. Wookiee eye colors are usually blue, green, yellow, golden, brown, or red.</string>
    <string name="wookie_info2">Wookiees greatly value honor and loyalty. Therefore, their notion of "family" encompassed much more than just blood ties. A part of that most sacred tradition was the social institution of life debt: when a wookiee\'s life was saved by someone else, regardless of the species, they would frequently devote themselves to a lifetime of service to their savior and their family. Through the mechanism of the life debt, the People of the Trees used to develop unbreakable bonds with their boon companions and true friends, forming a "honor family."</string>
    <string name="wookie_info3">Wookiee names are diverse; some names are simple and short while others are long and complicated. The majority of names often have softer big sounds and more melodic tones to them. Since offworlders have trouble using wookiees\' real names, they often adopt simpler nicknames to go by.</string>
    <string name="wookie_traitsHeader">Wookie Traits</string>
    <string name="wookie_traitsText">As a wookiee, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Strength score increases by 2, and your Constitution score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Wookiees reach adulthood at about 40 and can live to be 400.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Wookiees tend toward the light side, though there are exceptions.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Wookiees tend to tower over other species, reaching heights over 8 feet and weighing 300 pounds. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Claws</b>. Your claws are natural weapons, which you can use to make unarmed strikes. Additionally, your unarmed strikes deal 1d4 kinetic damage.\n"   " <b>Darkvision</b>. Your vision can easily cut through darkness. You can see in dim light within 60 feet of you as if it were bright light, and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can’t discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.\n"   " <b>Hide</b>. You have a thick hide. While you are unarmored or wearing light armor, your AC is 13 + your Dexterity modifier. Additionally, you have advantage on Constitution saving throws made to avoid exhaustion due to extreme cold.\n"   " <b>Menacing</b>. You have proficiency in the Intimidation skill.\n"   " <b>Powerful Build</b>. Your carrying capacity and the weight you can push, drag, or lift doubles. If it would already double, it instead triples.\n"   " <b>Treeclimber</b>. You have a climbing speed of 30 feet. You have advantage on Strength saving throws and Strength (Athletics) checks that involve climbing.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Shyriiwook. You can understand spoken and written Galactic Basic, but your vocal cords do not allow you to speak it.</string>
    <!--Zabrak-->
    <string name="zabrak">zABXAK</string>
    <string name="zabrak_example">Zabrak Example</string>
    <string name="zabrak_info1">Zabrak are near-human, but have a number of significant physical characteristics that set them apart from baseline Humanity. The most striking of these are a series of vestigial horns that crown the heads of both males and females. These horns grow at puberty in varying patterns and signified that their rite of passage is drawing near.\n"   " In addition to their horns, another of the traits that make zabrak instantly recognizable are their facial tattoos, which are made up of thin lines received during their rite of passage. These could symbolize many things, including but not limited to family lineage, place of birth, or even a design that reflected their individual personalities.\n"   " Lastly, zabraks possess a second heart.</string>
    <string name="zabrak_info2">Zabrak are often seen by most other species as being single-minded, an observation that is not terribly incorrect. This single-minded determination comes from the fact that they are a species with a strong sense of self-assuredness, confident that they are able to accomplish any task that they set out to do. However, this does not lead a zabrak to develop a sense of prideful superiority towards others. Though it is not uncommon to see competition between colonies, this is not seen as a negative. The zabraks believe that the various experiences of the different colonies only serve to add to the species\' overall value throughout the galaxy.</string>
    <string name="zabrak_info3">Zabrak names are usually derived from the animals living on their planet. Zabraks don\'t use surnames.</string>
    <string name="zabrak_traitsHeader">zabrak Traits</string>
    <string name="zabrak_traitsText">As a zabrak, you have the following special traits.\n"   " <b>Ability Score Increase</b>. Your Constitution score increases by 2, and your Strength or Dexterity score increases by 1.\n"   " <b>Age</b>. Zabraks reach adulthood in their late teens and live less than a century.\n"   " <b>Alignment</b>. Zabraks tend toward no particular alignment. The best and worst are found among them.\n"   " <b>Size</b>. Zabraks stand anywhere from 5 to 7 feet tall and weigh up to 300 lbs. Regardless of your position in that range, your size is Medium.\n"   " <b>Speed</b>. Your base walking speed is 30 feet.\n"   " <b>Coercive</b>. You have proficiency with Persuasion or Intimidation (your choice).\n"   " <b>Crafters</b>. You have proficiency with one set of artisan’s implements of your choice.\n"   " <b>Second Heart</b>. When you are reduced to 0 hit points but not killed outright, you can drop to 1 hit point instead. You can’t use this feature again until you finish a long rest.\n"   " <b>Toughness</b>. Your hit point maximum increases by 1, and it increases by 1 every time you gain a level.\n"   " <b>Unarmed Combatant</b>. Your unarmed strikes deal 1d4 kinetic damage and have the finesse property.\n"   " <b>Languages</b>. You can speak, read, and write Galactic Basic and Zabraki.</string>


    <!--utility stuff for Species-->
    <string name="traits">Traits</string>
    <string name="players_as_droids"><b><font size="18">PLAYERS AS DROIDS</font></b>\n"   " Work with your GM to determine if playing as a droid is appropriate for your campaign. Droids are impervious to many effects and vulnerable to others. If your GM approves this choice of species, Work with them to determine your droids designation, name, and appearance. If you want to play a different type of droid, work with your GM to find suitable traits to realize your character.</string>
    <string name="plus2d4inches">+2d4\"</string>
    <string name="plus2d6inches">+2d6\"</string>
    <string name="plus2d8inches">+2d8\"</string>
    <string name="plus2d10inches">+2d10\"</string>
    <string name="plus2d12inches">+2d12\"</string>
    <string name="two_foot_nine">2\'9\"/0,85m</string>
    <string name="two_foot_five">2\'5\"/0,75m</string>
    <string name="four_foot_three">4\'3\"/1,30m</string>
    <string name="four_foot_five">4\'5\"/1,45m</string>
    <string name="four_foot_six">4\'6\"/1,40m</string>
    <string name="four_foot_eigth">4\'8\"/1,40m</string>
    <string name="four_foot_nine">4\'9\"/1,45m</string>
    <string name="four_foot_ten">4\'10\"/1,45m</string>
    <string name="four_foot_eleven">4\'11\"/1,50m</string>
    <string name="five_foot_one">5\'1\"/1,55m</string>
    <string name="five_foot_two">5\'2\"/1,55m</string>
    <string name="five_foot_three">5\'3\"/1,60m</string>
    <string name="five_foot_five">5\'5\"/1,65m</string>
    <string name="five_foot_six">5\'6\"/1,65m</string>
    <string name="five_foot_eight">5\'8\"/1,70m</string>
    <string name="five_foot_nine">5\'9\"/1,75m</string>
    <string name="six_foot_three">6\'3\"/1,90m</string>
    <!--utility stuff for Tables-->
    <string name="info"><font color="#D4af37">Info</font></string>
    <string name="base"><font color="#D4af37">Base</font></string>
    <string name="tables"><font color="#D4af37">Tables</font></string>
    <string name="level">Level</string>
    <string name="profficiencybonus">Profficiency\nBonus</string>
    <string name="features">Features</string>
    <string name="table"><font color="#D4af37">Table</font></string>
    <string name="tech_powers_known">Tech Powers\nKnown</string>
    <string name="tech_points">Tech\nPoints</string>
    <string name="force_powers_known">Force Powers\nKnown</string>
    <string name="force_points">Force\nPoints</string>
    <string name="potent_aptitude">Potent\nAptitude</string>
    <string name="max_power_level">Max Power\nLevel</string>

    <!--utility stuff for Hub-->
    <string name="classbutton">cLASS</string>
    <string name="forcecasting">FoXcEcASTiNG</string>
    <string name="classes">cLASSES</string>
    <string name="species">SPEciES</string>

    <!--utility stuff for Equipment-->
    <string name="equipment_menu_weapon"><font color="#d4af37">Weapons</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_simple"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Simple</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_martial"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Martial</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_melee"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Melee</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_ranged"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Ranged</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_favorites"><font color="#D4af37">Favorites</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_armours_and_shields"><font color="#d4af37">Armours &amp; Shields</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_light"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Light</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_medium"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Medium</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_heavy"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Heavy</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_armours"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Armours</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_shields"><font color="#D4af37">"     "Shields</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_advgear"><font color="#d4af37">Adventuring Gear</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_ammunition"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Ammunition</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_communications"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Communications</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_data"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Data</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_life_support"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Life support</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_medical_supplies"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Medical supplies</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_storage"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Storage</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_utilities"><font color="#d4af37">"     "Utilities</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_accessories"><font color="#d4af37">"     "W&amp;A accessories</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_ok"><font color="#d4af37">Confirm Filters</font></string>
    <string name="equipment_menu_filters">Filters:</string>
    <string name="equipment">EquiPMENT</string>
    <string name="weapons">" WEAPoNS "</string>
    <string name="armour">AXMouX &amp; sHiELDS</string>
    <string name="adventuring_gear">ADvENTuXiNG GEAR</string>
    <string name="all_list">" ALL LiST "</string>
    <string name="eqerror404">Equipment not found</string>

    <!--Random utility stuff -->
    <string name="title_activity_classes">ClassesActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_SW5ECompanionApp">SW5ECompanionApp</string>
    <string name="app_name">Star Wars Companion App</string>
    <string name="star_wars_companion_app">Star Wars companion App</string>
    <string name="dummy">dummy</string>
    <string name="fab">FAB</string>
    <string name="menu">menu</string>
    <string name="plus2">+2</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="caster_level">Caster\nLevel</string>
    <string name="slot_level">Slot\nLevel</string>

    <string name="settings"><font color="#d4af37">Settings</font></string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="forcepower_name">Forcepower Name</string>
    <string name="details">details</string>
    <string name="forcepowererror404">Force power not found</string>
    <string name="favorite_button">Favorite Forcepower</string>
    <string name="text">Text</string>
    <string name="forcecasting_nosuchforcepower">No Such Forcepower Found</string>
    <string name="sampletext">Sample Text</string>
    <string name="attributes">Attributes</string>
    <string name="cost_amp_weight"><![CDATA[Cost & Weight]]></string>
    <string name="damageac">DamageAC</string>
    <string name="properties">Properties</string>
    <string name="expansion">Expansion</string>
    <string name="error_please_report_this">Error, Please report this to: #TODO</string>
    <string name="equipment_info_wealth1"><font size="28">T</font>he marketplace of a large city teems with buyers and sellers of many sorts: Jawas peddling refurbished wares (or trying to steal from careless travelers), Ugnauts selling various technology scrap, Twi\&#39;lek armstechs and Mirialan synthweavers. In the largest cities, almost anything imaginable is offered for sale, from exotic spices and luxurious clothing to speeders and spaceships.\n"    "For an adventurer, the availability of armor, weapons, backpacks, rope, and similar goods is of paramount importance, since proper equipment can mean the difference between life and death in a stronghold or the untamed wilds. This chapter details the mundane and exotic merchandise that adventurers commonly find useful in the face of the threats that the worlds of D&amp;D present.\n\n<b>Variant:Starting Wealth by Class</b></string>


</resources>